<sburb description='cronus dialogs'>
	<classes>
		<action sprite='karkat' class='tereziTalk1' command='talk' name='Talk to Terezi.'>
      <args>
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: TEREZI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE ASLEEP.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: SHRUG
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: WHY ARE YOU HERE ALL ALONE IN THE WOODS? OR THE PRETEND WOODS, I GUESS.
      @karkat_what KARKAT: AND WHY DO YOU HAVE YOUR DRAGON COSPLAY PULLED DOWN LIKE THAT? IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: NO
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: 1M F1N3
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU DON'T SOUND FINE. DON'T BULLSHIT ME LIKE THAT, I KNOW WHEN SOMETHING'S UP WITH YOU.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: K4RK4T PL34S3 JUST L34V3 M3 4LON3
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: OK, I GET IT IF YOU WANT SOME ALONE TIME. I MEAN, I ACTUALLY JUST GOT DONE SULKING THE FUCK OUT MYSELF JUST NOW. 
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: BUT IT REALLY HELPS TO TALK TO SOMEBODY. YOU CAN TALK TO ME ABOUT STUFF, YOU KNOW THAT RIGHT?
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: Y34H, 1 GU3SS
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: IS IT DAVE? DID HE DO SOMETHING DOUCHEY AGAIN?
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: ...
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: DID HE BREAK UP WITH YOU? HE BROKE UP WITH YOU, DIDN'T HE. I KNEW IT, I COULD JUST SEE THE WRITING ON THE WA...
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: H3 D1DNT BR34K UP W1TH M3!!!
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: 1T H4S NOTH1NG TO DO W1TH D4V3
      @karkat_what KARKAT: OK THEN WHAT
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: 1TS
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: MY 4NC3STOR
      @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: YEAH? WHAT ABOUT HER.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: SH3
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: SH3S JUST
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: SO
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: R4D1C4L >:[
      @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: HUH?
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: 1 JUST D1D NOT KNOW 1T W4S 3V3N POSS1BL3
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: TO B3 SO R4D
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: 1 4LMOST C4NT H4NDL3 1T K4RK4T
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: TH3 R4DN3SS
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: HOW DO3S SH3 DO 1T?
      @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: WELL, LET'S SEE. SHE RIDES A FUCKING SKATEBOARD. AND THAT'S IT. PRETTY MUCH END OF THE EXPLANATION.
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: 1 TH1NK 1T 1S SO MUCH MOR3 TH4N TH4T
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: 3V3RYON3 LOV3S H3R
      @terezi_sad TEREZI: SH3 1S SO S4SSY 4ND FUN, SH3S TH3 B3ST 4T G4M3S, 4ND 4LL H3R STUNTS 4R3 1NCR3D1BL3
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: HOW 4M 1 SUPPOS3D TO M34SUR3 UP TO TH4T?
      @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: OH COME ON
      @karkat_idle KARKAT: DON'T TELL ME THIS IS GOING TO BE A THING WITH YOU NOW.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: WH4T TH1NG?
      @karkat_idle KARKAT: A SELF ESTEEM THING.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T BE LIKE THAT, IT'S JUST SO UNWARRANTED.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: W3LL TH4TS HOW 1 F33L, SO TOO B4D!!!
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: TEREZI, I CAN'T STRESS THIS ENOUGH. YOU ARE *NOT* IN ANYONE'S SHADOW.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING ABOUT OUR ANCESTORS.
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: THEY'RE ALL ASSHOLES!!!
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: >:|
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: SH3 1S NOT 4N 4SSHOL3
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: NO, SHE IS. TRUST ME.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: THEY ALL ARE. AT LEAST THE VAST MAJORITY.
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: THEY PRACTICALLY AREN'T EVEN PEOPLE. THEY'RE WALKING, TALKING, LIKE...
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PUT IT. ALMOST LIKE LIVING PARODIES OF HORRIBLE, CLICHED BEHAVIOR PATTERNS.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: WH4T, YOU M34N L1K3...
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: T33N4G3RS?
      @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: YES.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: BUT IT'S MORE THAN JUST THAT. TAKE MY ANCESTOR FOR EXAMPLE.
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: TOTAL ASSHOLE! PROBABLY THE WORST ASSHOLE THERE IS.
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU WOULDN'T KNOW IT RIGHT AWAY BECAUSE I GUESS HE DOESN'T YELL AT PEOPLE LIKE ME? BUT THAT PROBABLY MAKES IT WORSE.
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: HE JUST GOES ON AND ON ABOUT THE MOST SANCTIMONIOUS, INCOMPREHENSIBLE GARBAGE YOU EVER HEARD. HE THINKS HE'S BETTER THAN EVERYONE BUT THEN DRESSES IT UP IN THIS BOGUS HYPER-ACADEMIC HUMILITY. HE TRIES TO DEFEND PEOPLE WITH "PROBLEMS" BUT JUST WINDS UP INSULTING THOSE PEOPLE IN BACKHANDED WAYS. HE LECTURES PEOPLE ENDLESSLY, AND WHENEVER HE RISES TO THE "DEFENSE" OF HIS FRIENDS HE USUALLY ENDS UP GIVING THEM A BIG FUCK YOU BY BEING IMPLICITLY JUDGMENTAL.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: I COULD REALLY GO ON FOREVER ABOUT HIM, BUT I WON'T, BECAUSE THEN I'D BE STOOPING TO HIS LEVEL.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: H3H3...
      @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: AND YOUR ANCESTOR? YEAH, SHE'S "FUN" I GUESS. BUT TALK ABOUT A PHONY.
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: OH AND I DON'T GIVE A *FUCK* WHAT ANYONE SAYS, LOSING YOUR SENSE OF SMELL IS NOT A REAL DISABILITY!!!
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: HER RAD GIRL THING IS SUCH AN OBVIOUS ACT. SHE'S CLEARLY WORKED FOR SWEEPS ON PERFECTING IT, AND QUITE APPARENTLY REVELS IN THE ATTENTION IT GETS HER.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: BUT THE FACT THAT SHE WORKS SO HARD ON IT IS EXACTLY WHY YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU DON'T EVEN NEED TO TRY TO BE THE GOOD PERSON YOU ALREADY ARE.
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: SEE, YOU ALREADY KNOW HOW TO HAVE FUN AND BE LIKABLE BY JUST BEING YOURSELF. IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE PART OF SOME OVER THE TOP SCHTICK TO IMPRESS PEOPLE. WHEN SHE DOES THE RAD GIRL THING IT'S LIKE A DISGUISE, PROBABLY COVERING UP SOME PART OF HERSELF SHE'S UNHAPPY WITH. BUT WHEN YOU WITHDRAW AND COVER YOURSELF UP LIKE THAT, YOU'RE ACTUALLY JUST PREVENTING PEOPLE FROM SEEING SOMEONE WHO'S ALREADY BEAUTIFUL.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: ...
      @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: I KNOW I COMPLETELY FUCKED UP WITH YOU. THIS ISN'T, UH... OK. I'M NOT LIKE TRYING TO REDEEM MYSELF HERE. I MADE MY RECUPERACOON AND NOW I HAVE TO WRIGGLE AROUND IN ITS SLIME. I TOTALLY ACCEPT THAT. BUT AS YOUR FRIEND I REALLY DON'T WANT YOU TO START FEELING BAD ABOUT YOURSELF BECAUSE OF ONE OF THESE SHALLOW, TWO DIMENSIONAL DIPSHITS. BUT I TOTALLY CONCEDE THAT YOU MADE YOUR CHOICE ABOUT ME, AND I RESPECT YOUR DECISION. I JUST WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY IS ALL.
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: ...
      @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: OK, I'M PROBABLY JUST STICKING MY FOOT IN MY FUCKING TALK BLASTER YET AGAIN, AND I'M PROBABLY MAKING YOU UNCOMFORTABLE. I GUESS I'LL GO BACK TO MY ROOM NOW. I HOPE YOU TAKE AT LEAST SOME OF WHAT I SAID SERIOUSLY THOUGH. 
      @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: UM. YEAH. OK, BYE.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='meenah' class='tereziTalk2' command='talk' name='Talk to Terezi.'>
      <args>
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: ps ur dragon outfit rules
      @terezi_idle TEREZI: >:]
      </args>
</action>
	</classes>
</sburb>
