<sburb><classes>

<action class='doorTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Open door.'><args>
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: vantas gimme your password
      @karkat_what KARKAT: (huh?)
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: this is your door aint it
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: (what makes you say that.)
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: the symbol on the doors the same as on your fuckin shirt
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#pchooo MEENAH: come on it aint blastoff device science
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: (ok, yeah, it's mine. maybe i got tired of interloping shitbags traipsing through my PRIVATE and PERSONAL memories.)
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you dont need to whisper anymore aint no one around
      @karkat_idle KARKAT: OH
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: now whats the password
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: MOVE OVER, I'LL TYPE IT FOR YOU.
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: no just tell me shouty!!! 
      @karkat_shout KARKAT: OH MY GOD, THAT IS SO UNREASONABLE. HOW IS IT NOT PRETTY MUCH THE MOST REASONABLE FUCKING THING IN THE WORLD TO LET ME JUST TYPE MY OWN PASSWORD???
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: dude you want kankri to find you and talk yer nubs off again
      @karkat_horror:#OH-DEAR-GOD KARKAT: NO!!! ANYTHING BUT THAT.
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: ALRIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU, JUST...
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: DON'T GO BLABBING IT AROUND.
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: THE PASSWORD IS...
      @karkat_eyeroll1~dialogimg_karkat1  
      @meenah_idle:#? MEENAH: wuh
      @karkat_eyeroll2~dialogimg_karkat1 
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: bro you gotta speak up
      @karkat_shout:#WHAT-ARE-YOU-DEAF KARKAT: IF I HATE MYSELF SO MUCH, THEN WHY DON'T I HATEMARRY MYSELF!!!!!!!
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: T)(ATS your p word
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: what in glubs name does that mean
      @karkat_yell KARKAT: NOTHING. IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: IT'S JUST SOMETHING THAT REMINDS ME OF AN OLD FRIEND. ALRIGHT?! CAN WE GET GOING NOW?
      @meenah_happier MEENAH: fuck yeah! this way shouty
      @meenah_creepytalk MEENAH: you will not regret hitchin your wagon to my starfish
      @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: 
      <!-- open the door -->
</args>
<action command='removeSprite'>
	<args>thirdRoomDoor,thirdRoom</args>
	<action command='addWalkable' noDelay='true'>
		<args>thirdRoomDoorWalkable,thirdRoom</args>
		<action command='playSound' noDelay='true'>
			<args>openSound2</args>
		</action>
	</action>
</action>
</action>

   <!-- if meenah talks to karkat (while kankri is away)-->
<action class='karkatTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Talk to Karkat.'>
	<args>
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: (psst!)
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: (hey vantas)
      @karkat_idle KARKAT: (what.)
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: (nows yer chance)
      @meenah_creepytalk:#nautical/popsicle...#eh-close-enough MEENAH: (lets blow this nautical stand)
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: (oh...)
      @karkat_talk KARKAT: (i don't think i'm supposed to.)
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: (shouty you cant let that boring nerd tell you how to roll)
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: (you wanna stand here lisfinin to his shellf important abaloney all day???)
      @karkat_eyeroll1:#SHELLF-IMPORTANT-ABALONEY?#GODDAMN-SEADWELLERS KARKAT: (not really.)
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: (then COM-E ON!)
      <!-- karkat then follows -->
	</args>
	<action command='follow'>
		<args>karkat,meenah</args>
		<action command='removeAction'>
			<args>thirdRoomDoor,Open door.</args>
			<action command='removeAction'>
				<args>karkat,Talk to Karkat.</args>
				<action command='addActions'>
					<args>thirdRoomDoor,
						<action class='doorTalk2'/>
					</args>
				</action>
			</action>
		</action>
	</action>
</action>

<action class='meenahTalk1' sprite='latula' command='talk' name='Talk to Meenah.'><args>
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: yo yo, p4ystubz my grrrl!
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: shit tules
      @meenah_talk:#passin-out-names-like-cheap-cuttlefish MEENAH: i forgot how many rad nicknames you like to cycle through 
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: you know i always thought paycheck was kind of dope why dont you just stick with that
      @latula_happier:#WOO LATULA: r1ght on! 1 l1k3 th4t on3 too, p4ych3ck 1t 1z. H1GH F1V3 GRL!!!
      @meenah_angry:#OOW MEENAH: no lets not OWWWWWW
      @latula_idle3:#>8( LATULA: ooh sorry, d1d 1 hurt you???
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: nnn... no? i meant
      @meenah_happier:#uh#yeah MEENAH: wwwwWOWWWWWW
      @meenah_ohyes MEENAH: like "WOWWWWW that was a radical hand slappin"
      @latula_happier:#th3-t1ghtn3ss LATULA: SUR3 FUCK1N WUZ!!! d4ng 1ts t1ght your3 b4ck.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: thats cool but
      @meenah_talk:#tadpole#yeah-its-a-stretch-as-a-fish-pun#gonna-count-it-tho MEENAH: arent you overstatin our prior relationship as somefin above neutral just a TAD
      @latula_annoyedtalk:#th3-b1g-w1p3out#r4d-d34th-4n4log13s LATULA: w3ll m4yb3. but 1 h4d 4 lot of t1m3 to th1nk, both b3for3 w3 4ll 4t3 1t, 4ND 4ft3r.
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: 4nd 1 c4m3 to som3 MAD 3p1ph4n13z, 4bout you, or us r34lly. 1 w4s th1nk1ng 4bout you 4ll wrong.
      @latula_angry LATULA: for most of th3 t1m3 w3 kn3w 34ch oth3r, 1 w4s 4ll l1k3, WHY SHOULD TH3R3 B3 TWO B4D4SS, 1N-YOUR-F4C3 GRLZ 1N TH3 GROUP???
      @latula_talk LATULA: sort of ov3rk1ll, r1ght?
      @meenah_idle:#u-searious? MEENAH: mehhh
      @latula_talk LATULA: 1 w4s k1nd of v13w1ng you 4s 4 comp3t1tor, 1n l1k3 4 two grl RAD-OFF. 1 w4s w1nn1ng 1n my m1nd, of cours3. but s33, 1 h4d 1t 4ll wrong!!!!
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: did you
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: Y3AH! s33, 1m th3 t34mz R4D GRL, wh3r34s YOUR3 th3 t34mz B4D GRL!!!! 1t 4ll m4k3s p3rf3ct s3ns3! do3snt th4t m4k3 SO MUCH S3NS3???
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: that
      @meenah_wut2:#p-lame-tules MEENAH: is the stupidest glubbin thing to require any sorta rationalization i ever heard
      @latula_laugh LATULA: s33 p4ych3ck? 1 kn3w 1 could count on you to b3 just1f14bly cyn1c4l 4bout my n3urot1c bullsh1t. you RUL3!!!
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='meenahTalk2' sprite='porrim' command='talk' name='Talk to Meenah.'><args>
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I really can't blame yo+u fo+r being in such a hurry to+ go+ kill him.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: huh
      @porrim_annoyed:#Sno+tty-brat-privilege PORRIM: The Lo+rd o+f Time. Actually, it's a go+o+d example o+f what I've always been trying to+ say to+ Kankri, but he do+esn't buy it.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: After the scratch, o+ur wo+rld co+ntinued to+ be matriarchal upo+n superficial o+bservatio+n, but was subject to+ a co+nsiderably mo+re sinister, clo+aked fo+rm o+f patriarchal tyranny all alo+ng.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: water you talking about
      @porrim_talk:#An-excellent-ho+st PORRIM: Yo+ur po+st-scratch self, who+ grew up to+ be the empress, was really just the Lo+rd's slave all alo+ng. Implicity during her lo+ng reign, thro+ugh manipulatio+n by his cunning emplo+yee. 
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: And then explicitly, after the extinctio+n o+f o+ur race. She fo+rmally became his servant, and did his bidding lo+ng thereafter.
      @meenah_angry MEENAH: W)(AT!!!!!
      @porrim_talk:#The-o+utco+me-was-so+mewhat-different-this-time PORRIM: He did the same with Damara. She was his lo+yal Time Witch, helping him turn o+ur wo+rld into+ the nightmare it became. When her usefulness came to+ an end, he pitted yo+u and her against each o+ther, in I guess a twisted redux o+f the co+nflict yo+u and she had in the past.
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: yo that is so messed up!
      @porrim_angrytalk PORRIM: The bo+tto+m line is, in additio+n to+ being an all aro+und bastard, this guy appears to+ enjo+y being especially nasty to+ girls.
      @porrim_surprisetalk PORRIM: If it's true he's hunting do+wn the gho+st o+f his departed "sister", then I really feel so+rry fo+r her.
      @meenah_angrytalk:#RARRRG)( MEENAH: NO FUCK T)(AT
      @meenah_angrytalk:#AARRRRAAAWWWRRG)(G MEENAH: I AM GOING TO SLAUG)(T-ER T)(AT UGLY MUSCL-E MONST-ER
      @meenah_angrytalk:#AAAUURGRURGGU)(G)()( MEENAH: I WILL ST-EAL )(IS S)(ITTY COAT AND W-EAR IT ON MY T)(RON-E
      @meenah_angrytalk:#ARRARARGLAAARUGRGURGGLE MEENAH: I WILL RIP OFF )(IS SKULL AND GILD IT AND T)(-EN I WILL W-EAR IT AS MY CROWN W)(IL-E )(IS BL-E-EDING GR-E-EN TORSO BOWS B-EFOR-E M-E
      @porrim_surprise:#wo+w PORRIM: Um,
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Best o+f luck with that.
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='meenahTalk3' sprite='kankri' command='talk' name='Talk to Meenah.'><args>
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Wh9a, Meenah. I didn't see y9u c9me in. Y9u sh9uld have c9me say hell9.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: oh
      @meenah_talk:#or-talk-to-or-listen-to-or-be-around-you MEENAH: yeah i didnt wanna bother you and shoutier you over there
      @kankri_talk:#s9-many KANKRI: It w9uld have 6een alright. Karkat and I were 9nly a few h9urs fr9m wrapping up 9ur first 9f what I'm presuming will 6e many, many sessi9ns t9gether.
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: Y9u and I have s9 much t9 discuss. I've really crystallized s9me pr96lems. Eternity has really helped me make s9me pr9gress 9n issues that matter t9 every69dy. Even gr9ups 9f pe9ple wh9 d9n't technically exist. 
      @kankri_talk4:#Herding-all-these-g9ddamn-w99l6easts#Fuckin-pain-in-the-ass KANKRI: I've had a l9t 9f time t9 think. A69ut that, and a69ut us. 9ur team, I mean, and the mistakes we've made which were pr96a6ly 6lessings in disguise. I kn9w we had 9ur differences, with y9u claiming the r9le as s9rt 9f 9ur defact9 leader, in terms 9f strategy and executi9n... literal executi9n, I supp9se. While I r9se t9 pr9minence am9ng 9ur peers as the undisputed spiritual shepherd 9f the gr9up. 
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: uh
      @meenah_happy:#undisputed-spiritual-shepherd?#ahahahahaha MEENAH: whatever you say
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: I've als9 heard y9u're recruiting mem6ers f9r a militia? An9ther 69ld endeav9r. N9t surprising, th9ugh. 6ef9re y9u em6ark, I d9 h9pe y9u'll set aside at least several sweeps t9 listen t9 s9me 9f my...
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: hey vantas
      @meenah_talk:#baited-like-worms-and-such#fishin#38) MEENAH: i really want to hear more of your garbage and lisfin to it all with hella baited breath
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: like i really really missed that you have no idea
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: but i have to go do
      @meenah_idle:#uh#yeah MEENAH: a thing
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: reel quick
      @kankri_idle KANKRI: 9h.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: can you wait
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: like right H-ER-E
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: exactly this spot
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: for a few minutes
      @kankri_idle KANKRI: A6s9lutely!
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: Really, n9 hurry, I'll take the time t9 prepare s9me 9f my 9pening statements t9 6etter c9ntextualize my pr9hi6itively l9quaci9us harangue. I mean friendly 6anter.
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: brb dog
      <!-- then "Be Meenah?" prompt -->
</args></action>

<action class='aradiaTalk1' command='talk' name='Talk.'><args>
      @aradia_happy ARADIA: greetings!
      @aradia_happytalk ARADIA: ive been meaning to say hello since you arrived
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: ...
      @meenah_angrytalk:#aw-hell-no MEENAH: M-EGIDO???
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: yes but not the one youre thinking of
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: which one then
      @aradia_talk:#you-know#the-afterlife? ARADIA: i like to consider myself as something of a caretaker for this place
      @aradia_laugh:#:D ARADIA: id refer to myself as an excellent host but that has become kind of a loaded phrase
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you look like megido
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: but you sure dont sound like any megido i know
      @aradia_idle ARADIA: i should hope not!
      @aradia_talk:#even-though-'time'-is-really-just-a-figure-of-speech-here ARADIA: anyway those of us who are concerned with the preservation of reality have been looking forward to this day for some time
      @meenah_wut:#the-sky-just-broke#stupid-fairy MEENAH: why would you be lookin forward to this shit
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: not the devastation so much as your arrival
      @aradia_happytalk ARADIA: you have some big plans yes?
      @meenah_annoyed:#maybe MEENAH: ...
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: whats it to you
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: oh nothing! i am merely extending the courtesy of a formal welcome
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: now off with you! go find your friends
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: that IS why youve finally come out of your palace isnt it?
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yeah
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#but-i-got-my-eye-on-you#megido-lookin-fairy MEENAH: guess ill get goin then
      @aradia_happy ARADIA: ta!
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='aradiaTalk2' command='talk' name='Talk.'><args>
@aradia_idle ARADIA: lost?
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: i uh
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: went the wrong way
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: yes thats a dead end
      @aradia_talk ARADIA: where you want to go is
      @aradia_point ARADIA: THAT way
      @aradia_wink:#double-pistols#and-a-;) ARADIA: *nk-nkt*
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: thanks
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: weirdo
</args></action>

<action class='andrewTalk1' command='talk' name='Talk.'>
	<args>
			@meenah_idle MEENAH: yo orange guy
			@meenah_idle MEENAH: or uh
			@meenah_idle:#squash-colored? MEENAH: yellow guy
			@! .............
			@meenah_idle:#what-the-fuck-is-with-all-these-8-balls MEENAH: whats your deal
			@meenah_idle MEENAH: are you uh
			@meenah_idle:#awkward MEENAH: crying?
			@! SILENCE.
			@! Bring me a horse, and I am yours forever.
			<!--  -->
	</args>
</action>

<action class='andrewTalk2' command='talk' name='Talk.'>
	<args>
			@! Oh my god, you didn't.
      @!:#could-it-be? You DIDN'T......
      @! _YOU DID_
      @! YOU BROUGHT ME A HORSE!
      @! Look at this glorious, knotted up horse hitcher. This is the most amazing present I have ever received. I will cherish it forever.
      @! So uh, hey...
      @!:#Vriska-WHO????? Do you come here often?
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: oh my cod
      @! Well, a deal is a deal.
      @! I am now at your command.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: why...
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: WHY did i have to bring this idiot that horse hitcher
      <!--  -->
	</args>
	<action command='removeAction'>
		<args>andrew,Talk.</args>
		<action command='follow'>
			<args>andrew,meenah</args>
			<action command='deltaSprite'>
				<args>questSwitch,20,0</args>
			</action>
		</action>
	</action>
</action>
</classes></sburb>
