<sburb>
<classes>
<action class='redBubbleText'><args>
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey so what sort of insane loot did you rake in today
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just found an unopened container of apple juice in my closet it is like fucking christmas up in here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you suggesting someone put piss in my apple juice at the factory
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why did the fat kid or whoever drank it know what piss tasted like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean his reaction was nigh instantaneous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok i can accept that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: monster B-list celebrity douchebags are cunning and persistent pranksters
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also fred savage has a really punchable face
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but who cares about this lets stop talking about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you see how it got slammed in game bro????
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why dont you go check your mail maybe its there now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: plz say yes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shes mackin on me so hard all the time i start to feel embarrassed for her
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean not that i can blame her or anything
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thank you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whats your modus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: how do you retrieve artifacts from it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stack?? hahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hash map
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my bro taught me a few tricks he basically knows everything and is awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you should probably brush up on your data structures
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: plus let you attack stuff whenever things get too hot to handle which is never
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wow you really suck at this dont you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just get rid of the arms and then allocate the hammer to the specibus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know just use the arms on any old thing and see if it works
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess i should have mentioned that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hope you like hammers dude!
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey GG is looking for you why are you even so popular all of a sudden
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is today some sort of special occasion or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you do something to curry favor with ladies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you break your leg on a puppy or some shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude what are you doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no stop
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just no
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont talk about your awful stupid movies or make references to them
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: your gross man-bro crush on matt macconahay is an unsavory thing to behold
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sounds like a noise a horse would make ie dumb
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: equally dumb are all those pictures of that clown youve got hanging up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was talking about nick cage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ha ha so lame
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont even like him ironically or anything this is like for real isnt it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no those are awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im wearing them ironically
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: because theyre awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the fact that theyre ironic makes them awesome and vice versa
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you taking notes on how to be cool?? jesus get a fucking pen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ew yeah
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh well
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anyway speaking of which
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: haha no way
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it sounds so HELLS of boring just get TT to play it she is all about that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: her internet is blinking in and out i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh and christ in a sidecar are you still using the stack modus???
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: seriously dude
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you need to BONE UP on your data structures that shit is just ridiculous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i hope you appreciate my heroic fatherly perseverance in getting it to you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in my rough and tumble dirty wifebeaterly sort of way
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also i hope you appreciate how many no-talent douches had their mitts on that bunny before you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like a grubby baton in some huge douchebag marathon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey where are you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude i told you to steer clear of that game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and for that matter you should probably wash your hands of flighty broads and their snarky horseshit altogether
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: how big is it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like the size of texas
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or just rhode island
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theyre always throwing around these geographical comparisons to give us a sense of scale like it really means anything to us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but its like it doesnt matter its always just like: WOW THATS PRETTY FUCKING BIG
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like mr president theres a meteor coming sir. oh yeah, how big is it? its the size of texas sir
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: OH SHIT
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or, how big is it? its the size of new york city sir
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: OH SHIT
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sir im afraid the comet is the size of your moms dick
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: OH SNAP
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sir are you familiar with jupiter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you mean like the planet?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well its that big sir
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hmm that sounds pretty big
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i have a question
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is it jupiter?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes sir, earth is literally under seige by planet fucking jupiter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: OH SHIT
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anyway later
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey bro check it out im working on some new rhymes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: come on this is hells of ill just listen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: huh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for real
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i think i could drop some sick rhymes about all this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no thisll be dope check it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait wait
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: armageddon's gettin waged on us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but im-a gettin armed and dangerous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sending men in space for savin us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see which playa's more couragerous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ben or bruce? dudes reach a truce
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: put their blowchutes to use and up-suck it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: afflecks saclifice, i mean -crifice, would have to sufflice. aw fluck it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bro be a stained-glass saint, up on a cross gettin hella christ-plagiarous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bruce's like offa that cruciflix, nuff a this fuckin savior-fuss
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: restrained his ass per mclane-redux while buscemi remained derangerous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: when a plan gone astray pays off a wasted craterous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ash tray caterin to layers of matt maconnaheys vague remainder-dust
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: uh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: macconahey wasnt even in any of those meteor movies was he
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill have to make a rap about
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: morgan freeman or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: being the president
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: itll be called
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: "obama made it so that no one gives a shit about black presidents in movies anymore"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see youve got to fill me in on whats going on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so i have something to rap about besides all your dumbshit movies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: when the film crew zooms where the presidents at
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im like if that dudes black ill eat my hat
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: turns out he is, so we're all "damn, director's got gumption"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like we'll all flip our shit he aint shining shoes or somethin
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its called freemancipation. if its not pres-election its god-ascension
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in bruce almighty. whoops, different bruce from the one i just mentioned
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cant explain to me why this aint condescension to think ill shit a brick
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: not even he can convey the intention with his quickspun wit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: rather defray all this tension, sit on his lap while he whittles a splint
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and some guy eyes what he does and patronizes: i guess negrocity's the mother of invention
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whats up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats going to be tough
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i lost it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a stupid story and id rather not talk about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shit be embarrassing yo
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: one is my brothers copy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alright
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but hes not gonna be happy about that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nothing really
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: look all im saying is the girl tends to lay it on kinda thick you know? 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what oh no
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no look
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im busy ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ive got a lot of shit on my plate
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am sort of a big deal ok?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: seriously
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dudes be worshipping me left and right
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant hardly walk down the street without stepping over torsos of the prostrate
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean damn
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like theres this scruffy little shit at my feet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: an orphan or something i dont know
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: face flush on the pavement
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im like dude you listening for a stampede of buffalo or something?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he braves a look at me then gives my shoe a little kiss and scurries the fuck off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: not kicking oliver twist in the fucking face every day is my gift to the world i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: among other things
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just give and fucking give
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh for fucks sake
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre just lobbying for me to play that dumb game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: look i am telling you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: egbert is ALL ABOUT that game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he will play it with you and probably be tickled retarded about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah yeah
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill hassle him some more about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and look how about this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if you ever find yourself in the position where your life depends on me playing that piece of shit game, then ill play
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: will that make you happy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey sup
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: haha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: good one
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: s'alright being chill i guess you know how it goes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man you know it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you know shit is ice cold up in here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shit is wicked bananas i am telling you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah we were just talking a while ago about how he sucks at his sylladex
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: can you believe he uses stack that kid is ridiculous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what was it you use again...
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait nm
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i forgot whenever we talk about your goofy modusses i get a migrane. what do you want with john
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was being sort of cagey and told him to check the mail cause i was wondering if mine came yet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess you want to know if he likes it or something?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wow sorry to hear that i guess?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i never get how you know these things
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if i were you i would just take that fucking devilbeast out behind the woodshed and blow its head off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but he sounds like a total badass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im out of my room now looking for my bros game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you better know what youre talking about cause this could get ugly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: brought my phone and i also took my awesome katana with me in case things get too hot to handle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and they always do
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: FU
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its sharp and its awesome and its a sword
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: end of story
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: howie???
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude monsters arent real
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats stupid kids stuff for stupid babies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what are you an idiot
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: of course there are monsters in your house
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre in some weird evil monster dimension come on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: skepticism is the crutch of cinematic troglodytes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like hey mom dad theres a dinosaur or a ghost or whatever in my room. "yeah right junior go back to bed"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuck you mom and dad how many times are we going to watch this trope unfold it wasnt goddamn funny the first time i saw it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just once id like to see dad crap his pants when a kid says theres a vampire in his closet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: "OH SHIT EVERYONE IN THE MINIVAN"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: be fuckin dad of the year right there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what do you have a hammer
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man so lame
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my bro is always getting on my case about it but man its not as easy as it sounds
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but if youre fighting monsters left and right you dont have much choice
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im out in the living room hes usually here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: might be playing his mind games hes always pulling this ninja shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all i see is lil cal over there so i guess he cant be far
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh lil cal? no man
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lil cal is the shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cal is dope
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: puppets are awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john egbert blows
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the end
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john said your house was burning down are you on fire yet or what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john told me to get the game to help get you out of there so im working on that now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah my bros copy long story
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont tell john this but i think he might have been right about the puppets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theyre sort of starting to freak me out a little
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean dont get me wrong i think its cool and all
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the semi-ironic puppet thing or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or semi-semi ironic
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man i dont even know
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im just starting to think some of this shit is going a little far and its kind of fucked up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: haha yeah well YOU WOULD
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man i wish lil cal wouldnt look at me like that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with those dead eyes jesus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sometimes i dream that hes real and hes talking to me and i wake up in a cold sweat and basically flip the fuck out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh god why did i just tell you my dream
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre going to have a field day with that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah im gonna get moving
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hes not answering me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alright im out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: later
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what happened with the monster that is totally definitely in your room did you kill it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where are you man
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: things are cool here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: puppets are still awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no problems with them or anything
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: really really awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok wait hold on why am i getting this stupid game for you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre the one who should be wrist deep in puppet ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the problem is i am up to my goddamn neck in fucking puppet dong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am enrobed in chafing, wriggling god fucking damned puppet pelvis
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: an obscenely long, coarse kermit cock is being dragged across my anguished face
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont seem to harbor any sympathy for the fact that ive burrowed fuck deep into lively, fluffy muppet buttock
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im whirling in the terrible cyclone at the epicenter of my own personal holocaust of twitching foam noses
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like a fucking apocalypse of perky proboscis here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the proboscalypse i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no listen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no oh jesus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok dickinson if you can shut your perfumey trap for a half second
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is serious
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am just saying
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if i see one more soft bulbous bottom being like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kind of jutting out and impudent or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im gonna fly off the handle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im gonna do some sort of acrobatic fucking PIROUETTE off the handle and win like a medal or some shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: PUPPETS
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: AWESOME
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: THATS REALLY ALL THERE IS TO SAY ON THE MATTER 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: THATS REALLY ALL THERE IS TO SAY ON THE MATTER 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre asleep again arent you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or do you even know if you are
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i still dont know how that works
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like nothing means anything
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its so cool getting hella chumped by your coquettish damn riddles all the time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know why i believe anything you say im like the grand marshal of gross chumpage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: assitant director of chumpography
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: celebrated author ernest chumpingway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait weak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: chumpelstiltskin
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: chumpeldipshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre asleep y//n?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a//s//l?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: s = species
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: baboon?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kangaroo rat?
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if kangaroo rat yiff twice plz
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok well youre not saying anything so i guess whether youre nonawake or unasleep or whatever youre just not around and im wasting good material
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: even worse im wasting a killer fursona here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know like a wide open v shaped leotard and a fuck ton of body paint
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: some like sinewy back arching cirque du soleil looking motherfucker
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: always low to the ground gettin a good prowl on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like i dropped my keys in the dark
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nimblest son of a bitch who had the gumption to glue a nasty pair of latex cat lips to his face
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for a reason that wasnt a joke
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: jade hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: seriously im sitting here tonight with a fucking bag of kibble jacked open on my lap and primed for goddamn bear
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: btw my name is Akwete Purrmusk
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hardest buttock in the jungle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: tempered steel
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey yeah just wanted to give you this remix i finished
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont have to respond to any of that btw
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill probably forget half the shit i said anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: talk to you tomorrow
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bro just kicked my ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats really all there is to say on the matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok i got it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i hope you appreciate how much gross spongy proboscis i had to fellate to get this game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: later
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my god you type like a tool
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is so weak im almost getting tired of wasting good material on you guys
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youve got nothing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its always one of you sprouting up and ranting about how hard im about to get trolled
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with no ensuing substance
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont even know anything about us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: one of you fuckers thought i was a girl
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sorry i wouldnt cyber with you dude
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in the future or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: human innuendo
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so at what point in the future am i supposed to look forward to you whipping up this titanic hankerin for my knob
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: be honest with me cause im busy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and i want to know exactly when i got to clear some space in my calendar for when some fuckwit blunders out of a magical phone booth and makes a ballad-inspiring play for my throbbing beef truncheon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and i want to know exactly when i got to clear some space in my calendar for when some fuckwit blunders out of a magical phone booth 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and makes a ballad-inspiring play for my throbbing beef truncheon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: some fuckwit blunders out of a magical phone booth and makes a ballad-inspiring play for my throbbing beef truncheon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no man
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just need to know when to be there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: when the stars come into alignment and your flux capacitor lets you finally sate your meteoric greed for crotch-dachshund
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: meteoric greed for crotch-dachshund
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i wouldnt want to miss it and cause a paradox or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: itd suck if the universe blew up on account of you missing your window of opportunity to help yourself to a pubescent boy's naked spam porpoise
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: missing your window of opportunity to help yourself to a pubescent boy's naked spam porpoise
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a pubescent boy's naked spam porpoise
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: jesus you are such a shitty troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no dude
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you sassed me up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we are in THE SHIT now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for the long haul
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we're motherfuckin entrenched in this bitch
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welcome to nam
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: now grab my hand and shimmy your soggy ass off that muddy bank before charlie gets the fuckin drop
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hes the guy whos gonna read our vows
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im feeling pretty friggin MATRIMONIAL all a sudden
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: take a look down by your foot see that little bottle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stomp on that shit like its on fire
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: noisy ethnic dudes are flipping the fuck out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and waving us around on chairs til someone gets hurt
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im your 300 pound matronly freight-train
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and my gaping furnace is hungry for coal so get goddamn shoveling
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bro look in my eyes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that twinkle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that be DEVOTION
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: herniated pro wrestlers sweaty purple taint
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sparklin like a visit from your fairy fuckin godmother
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shit be PURE AND TRUE
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a kaleidoscopic supernova of all your hopes and dreams all swishin together
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: radially effevescing arms of more little boy peckers than you can imagine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: turning out insane corkscrew haymakers of a billion dancing vienna sausages strong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is how we do this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this shits more real than kraft mayo
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you could almost say
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where making this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: TRANSPIRE
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: will you open your laptop already
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is why you need a phone or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: instead of leaving them trapped under three inches of fucking yarn
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: laptops dont need cozies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nothing needs cozies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cozy is a goddamn adjective
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe ill crochet myself an iphone snuggly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what is this place anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i can see your whole damn house here if you want to get filled in or something im sort of the guy with the big picture here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont make me bop you on the head with a wizard
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess ill bone up on the faq for a while
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so i dont do anything stupid and deploy like 10 crux flangers and fuck up the whole game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my god
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so many words
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you think like the pulitzer committee is secretly scouring the dregs of the gamefaq archives or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant read this shit im sorry
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whoa ok hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but she wont answer me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pretty much you have no idea how much i fuckin own at this game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i bested no less than three flaming tornados and broke a huge wizard
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am in sports
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all alone
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and i am the star
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and then the big man comes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we're good
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: reference secured
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is ridiculous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: some double duty thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean i own at the game and all but cant i just relax for half a second
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: look i was getting my ass handed to me by my bro on the roof for like an hour and a half
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i got served like a dude on butler island
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i got served like a dude on butler island
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i got served like a dude on butler island
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait does this mean theres a big meteor coming soon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you totally sure about all this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok yes that image is definitely conclusive proof of something and is 100% understandable by anyone who looks at it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: how big is this thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like the size of rhode island or texas or what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i need some context to know how much crap i should be shitting into my pants
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well as if like one the size of a bus wouldnt kill me anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait hold on rose is finally opening her stupid laptop
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so do your thing i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: have fun
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hold what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i see you at your computer typing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what are you doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dang
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no seriously stop talking to me for a second it looks like jade is dropping the doomsday tube thingy in my room
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: brb gotta make sure she doesnt break all my shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i always keep birds in here its sort of my thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no no thats irony this is like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sincere honest to god psychosis
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im training to be a lame gothy supervillain
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well maybe you should take the opportunity to put it somewhere that isnt stone cold retarded!
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know how does she do any of the loopy batshit nonsense she does
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe she pulled them out of the volcano over there on bloodmonkey mountain
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we went over this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was a little bogged down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in the epic swaddle of legendary puppet taint
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in the epic swaddle of legendary puppet taint
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the hell is she doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shes taking my bed what the hell
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so seriously what were you doing just now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: who
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you opted to chat up one of those dbags instead of talk to the guy who saved you from a swirling shitstorm of angry flaming wizards
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was worried your priorities might have been out of whack but no i was dead wrong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i should probably text him soon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: because
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i love him
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so this place youre at now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is the worst shitting thing ive ever seen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is the worst shitting thing ive ever seen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is the worst shitting thing ive ever seen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the thing that just happened
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: jesus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and the worst thing is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all that juice i drank
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you just HAD TO FIGURE all that juice was going to come back to haunt me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like frankensteins incontinent fucking ghost
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: chekhovs juice
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: let me be perfectly clear
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what i am trying to say is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like fucking christmas up in my bladder here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and where do i find my toilet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: amputated in my room
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: gagged with a towel like a fucking prison hostage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and now the cruxploder is counting down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: 4 hours oh i guess thats not that bad
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you asleep
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok lets just
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: not panic here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets try to play it cool
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and not break all my shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also dont put anything weird in the seizure kernel
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im going to go find somewhere to pee
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont watch me ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like i know you dream about me enough already
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets keep some shit left to the imagination ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the last thing i need is for your weird brain webcam to be snapping shots of my dong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: your grandpa was a sick fuck why would he build a voyeurbot for a little girl
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuck
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what bird
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i wouldnt know anything about that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that could be anyones sword
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what does it look like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is it a cheap piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cause i only bother with high quality blades
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: forged by stoic asian masters
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hells of rude kinds of expensive
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dammit hold on a minute
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wow awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so now i guess instead having of a wise or helpful spirit guide sprite thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im stuck with this brainless feathery asshole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre not very logical like this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kind of dumb really
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah but come on you sleep like 20 hours a day
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where are you sitting
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you on your bed
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok heres what i want you to do
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just humor me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: raise your left hand
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just kind of swat the air to your left
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its awesome where you put that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was worried we were on the verge of getting some shit done
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you say there will be stairs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i see no stairs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sorry
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: am i supposed to break that thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or hatch it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also what happened to all my shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the stuff scattered all over the roof
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you put it somewhere
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean not that i care
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it was a lot of mostly useless garbage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was going to use it to fight my bro with
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but i guess i forgot in the heat of battle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also he was too fast
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the egg is now in a nest made of shitty swords and soft puppet ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you think thatll take more than four hours
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its hot as the sizzle side of the steak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe i should try to get it back
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and put it in the microwave 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you mean the jumper block thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man i only got 200 to splash around with in roses rainbow world
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hang on ill ask
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so i guess you can buy everything now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok now i know youre making this shit up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well all i got here is the designix which i cant deploy cause i dont have any purples
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and the expensive as hell jumper thing and the cheap shunts which i assume do dick all without the jumpers to put em on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh also this cd which is 100 but i didnt drop cause it seemed like a stiff allocation of resources for now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey look we're learning stuff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wow that was a weird answer
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: which is sort of cool i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: since i wont have to go downstairs and bang the hallway door into the thing and squeeze through every time i want to punch a card
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: because of course you couldnt have just put it next to the alchemiter in the first place
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but then i have to go downstairs anyway to make totems and get cruxite and stuff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so really who cares 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im building up your house
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: by the way why do you live in this weird compound
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you host east european industrial raves
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nevermind the point is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so if youre done whipping that ogre like a rented mule
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know beach the thing first i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: unless you were planning on sailing that ogre down the mississippi with a runaway slave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: release a shitload of grist
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe take one of your needles and puncture the base of its skull
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: does it even have a skull
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or a brain stem
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but you just rigged the thing with an oedipal harness and rode its torso like a log flume ride down a magical rainbow
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is bullshit its an unfeeling monster who gives a fuck
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wow fuck ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you can either kill it for the loot or wait a couple hours for gristtorrent to steal more of johns
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but then again ill be pretty busy in a couple hours so make up your mind
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no but hes still got a ton so screw him
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: who
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i command her alright i am like the pimpmaster hustledaddy of all snippy bookshrews
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wrong what do you want
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the hell
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you have no idea dude she is so in my grill
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like a stray hotdog that rolled down there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and now its too much trouble to fish out with the tongs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so you just watch it like crack and turn black
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you have a thing for her dont you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont deny it bro its obvious
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hahahaha so terrible
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what a transparent dodge
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all hiding behind your alien shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you want me to help you win her over
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for everything she says take her to mean just the opposite
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see not everybody always means literally what they say the way john and jade always do
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my flipping christ
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok if you want rose to dig you you got to leave that crap in the shitty scifi novels where it belongs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe even too deadpan but its a start keep at it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hahaha yes youre on a roll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alright look
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if you want to keep her attention you got to pull out all the stops
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: reverse psychology mind games all sorts of machiavellian bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean unless youre really smooth and inherently likeable like me which youre not
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean unless youre really smooth and inherently likeable like me which youre not
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats kind of the obtuse alien way of getting it but yeah
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: an antagonism ninja
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know you sort of remind me of her anyway so maybe thats a good thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it could be a horrible thing though
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess im saying be a less shitty troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: good luck bro
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont care
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok im in
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what do you mean already shit took 4 goddamn hours
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont want to talk about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: imagine the worst day of my life
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just stood up and clinked a glass like it was about to give a speech
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then took a shit in my dinner and passed out with its pants down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stfu
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i need some advice
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my kernelsprite which was this brainless feathery asshole with a sword in it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: turned into this bigger like ghostly feathery asshole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with a sword in it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shes asleep for some reason
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all tuckered out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like she got smacked in the face with a pillow case full of the snooze wizards beard dander
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cause obviously its fuckin prime time for swiping some shuteye about now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like a few hours into her magic stupid quest
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anyway what do you think
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess im kinda weirded out by its suggestion
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok well it definitely sounds like youre fucking something up over there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but alright later 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shut up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: god damn it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: please
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just once
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shut the hell up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shut up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats it i cant take it anymore
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it was such a huge mistake prototyping seppucrow with this useless mindnumbing jackass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im going back
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what do you mean already shit took 4 goddamn months
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know im kind of losing track of how long its been with all this time hopping
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we lost
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cant finish the game with a dead heir and witch
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah well she had a big fucking meteor bearing down on her and we never heard from her again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or the trolls for that matter
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess once they managed to sabotage us they were done with us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theres not much to remember
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i go back and tell john not to be an idiot and get trolled like such a gullible stooge
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know what he was thinking
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: even we couldnt kill one of those things yet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with our higher levels and all our sick gear
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the thing with time travel is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you cant overthink it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just roll with it and see what happens
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and above all try not to do anything retarded
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the true purpose is to make a sprite that doesnt make me want to flog myself raw with my own brain stem
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anything else is gravy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah thatd be cool i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: WAIT
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: somethings up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he says i dunno gullible enough to trust a leetspeaking troll who wants you dead and strap on a rocket pack cause she said to
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok that was probably the dumbest thing you ever said just now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you hear what youre saying oh my god
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this guy is me if i get him to talk to you youre just talking to me again jesus it proves nothing 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john stop being a tool and unbuckle yourself from that piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if our friendship means anything youll listen to me and past dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is future dave by the way
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this sort of cornball horseshit is your cup of tea not mine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont make me track you down through time and stop you in person
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh god did you just blast off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im turning this timeline over to past dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and helping you all stay alive and do this thing the right way this time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just stay on the goddamn ground for fucks sake 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sup
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sup
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont talk to john anymore hes an impressionable doofus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so you might as well quit trying
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre aliens do you even have orange creamsicles
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok pretty far fetched but whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you DID kill him sort of
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then i went back in time to stop him
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you guess that by trolling john to his grave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and making me splinter us off into an alt timeline
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that you were basically complicit in making our timeline go the way it was supposed to go all along
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where future me is now helping dave and we just keep playing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thus leading you all to troll us incompetently
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: none of you ever thinks anything through
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whos in charge of timeline management there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i gotta give him the business
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well at least you got john to off himself so i guess youre not totally incompetent like the others
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like that awful rapper
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: huge pushover
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he will do what you say
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then all a sudden hes a tough nut to crack go figure
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah thats fine i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no more coy bullshit antics though
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: an idiotic angry winking emote
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just merged with an impaled orange goddamn bird and now i got all these crazy powers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh jegus fuck no
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why would that breathtaking douche remind you of me at all
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: now i know youre bullshitting me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do i seem like the kind of guy whod accept a magic ring from whoopi goldberg
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: to awaken some egregious homofantasy for a ripped blue dudes mammoth eco friendly bulge
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that guys an asshole and needs to be sealed in a dufflebag and whipped something ungodly with a bamboo chute
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: who cares
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok yeah that is pretty much fucking spot on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre actually a pretty good troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: who were you talking to
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just telling a troll to step off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so now that youre a sprite
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you know everything about the game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well i knew a lot anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cause im from the future
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but yeah i know more stuff now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess riddles
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im supposed to be cagey about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but i dont really feel like it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ask me anything go ahead ill give you a straight answer
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why are we so fucking awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why are we so fucking awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why are we so fucking awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why are we so fucking awesome
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the best fucking question anybody ever asked
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the best fucking question anybody ever asked
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the best fucking question anybody ever asked
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if not then we just bail everyone out yet again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all that gear you picked up should let you breeze through the first couple gates
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and well take care of shit together
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill go kill some time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe draw some comics
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was in the middle of the nancho party arc
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i gave up on that half way through
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: making a ten part story about nachos was always a bullshit idea
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets do some brainstorming later
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: blow everyones minds
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you blast off like a spazzy douche yet or what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: god dammit what do i have to do to make you believe me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fist bump my future self til i got bloody knuckles and write you an even sappier bday note in my own blood
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: him turning into a floating sword bird
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man and if weve just concluded anything its that talking to those dbags should be priority number one so yeah go right ahead
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also you suck at rockets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude you did go through the second gate
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean i dont know why you would listen to her again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kind of moronic but thats a whole other issue
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what were you expecting
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but shes sleeping pretty hard obviously
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but you got your cheat rocket so thats fine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am the real dave
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im more real actually cause ive been through some heavy shit already hopping around on red hot gears and i-beams for like a year
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and grinding shit out for your ungrateful ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: here look check out this code from the future not that you deserve it WIin189Q
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre fucking welcome 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yo
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what did you do
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cause i wouldnt give a shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dave is here he wants to use the computer
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: probably to help you scope out roses room and snoop and stuff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: use these flappy ghost wings and tear shit up in space or something 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok i dont know what youre doing here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but i think we can both agree that youve got to rummage through as much of her shit as possible before she wakes up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude no come on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shes out like a light anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it was some like weird future thing that happened that made her sleep
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shit doesnt get more clear than that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fine dont
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but here just do this one thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what kind of prying tool do you take me for
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you know like tidy up a bit since you made a royal fucking dump of her room just now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is important
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: flip it over
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just flip it over and let me know if theres a code there thats all
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alright cool
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you can ditch the books now if you want
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe put them back on the floor
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so rose doesnt think you were snooping
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: seriously youve got some grubby fingers bro why dont you mind your own business there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what is even with you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: isnt that your birthday package there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: afdsjjjjjjjjvfffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: really powerful hammer
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: got it from hephaestus
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: really tough to kill dude
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whoa why are you burning your wizard fanfiction
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is that some dumb wizard thing you just made up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or something to do with tentacle monsters
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant keep track of what you like anymore
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he was all snoopin around your room while you were asleep and i was like no man dont
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then he was like haha dude check it out this book is full of wizard slash
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and i was like i dont even want to know this is such a crazy violation of privacy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do you want me to chew him out about it i will because that was so outrageous i dont know where he got off being like that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i thought you hated wizards
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man thats so messed up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: she probably digs wizards for real just like you and youre blowing shit out of proportion like pretty much always
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you and she could probably have been chatting up how awesome wizards were this whole time but no
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre probably burning your nutjob meow book to spite her too arent you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i thought that was a joke
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you mean when we were dancing and stuff in our dreams
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no what a ridiculous question
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ....
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ........
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ..........................
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dunno
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: get some sky monsters to boss me around sounds cool
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that book was completely pointless
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you remember the future
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so why is the cat code so terrible now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but they sort of freak me out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean listening to gross space mutants all day isnt my idea of an awesome time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: especially the ones that sing oh god
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no i flip out to ill jams because they kick ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah case the fuck closed 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok im out of the loop again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: between you taking orders from dream beasts and bird wing me with like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: future secrets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im doing some sort of spectacular fucking jackknife off the loop and getting a wink and a nod from barack obana
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i know its crazy what kind of foresight this guy has
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im telling you coincidences like that are unreal they dont even happen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the best thing about how i did that is how it in no way will ever come back to bite us in the ass ever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude our shit is SAFE
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: gonna sleep pretty sound tonight
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with that big fucking payload of safety you just got dropped on us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: gonna be all huggin my pillow and shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: grinning like a goddamn bear full of honey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: safer than some flintstone vitamins in a bottle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: keep twisting junior all you get is clicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: asshole thinks its candy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: doesnt even know he just stepped on a security rake and got a face full of fucking safety
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where do you even get a burn thats that sick
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did you try to draw shades on his face and miss
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is moronic
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like a fuckin symphony on my retinas
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shit is beautiful like a little vermilion picnic on my hands
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: every day i open my eyes i find poetry in even the simplest things
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this miraculous gift of vision
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i could give myself a hernia trying to be as big a douche as that guy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i could try but it would wind up like a motorcycle stunt gone horribly wrong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my broken body would flop and tumble around like a rag doll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and yet as much as that guys the tooliest dude i could ever hope to meet he and i would still get along famously
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: havin a see party
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like a couple of eagle eyed bros peepin shit up into the wee hours
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess but youll have to be careful not to stumble around bumping into all the gorgeous masterpieces hanging around everywhere
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: god so beautiful to look at with my perfect eyesight
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok thats pretty amazing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my face doesnt make sense
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ew
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so the dumbest and most far fetched explanation imaginable ok got it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so embarrassing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we have cotton candy dumpass 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man who cares
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its just regular old time travel
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just regular ordinary dave from the fucking future nothing special dude come on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i need to borrow some boondollars off you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what do you think they buy shit its fucking money
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if theres one thing im not short on its the fuckin future
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but chronologically ive been around for at least triple that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre on easy street what is there even to think about with wind
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like what angle to blow it at to fly a damn kite or how gentle its gotta be to make a picnic go swimmingly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its kiddie bullshit time is serious fucking business
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this whole operation is strung together with stable time loops
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no timeline offshoots cause thats when daves start dying and that isnt no good for nobody
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: there are a bunch of daves running around the timeline
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man dont even get me started with that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know man they seem to flock to me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ive been laying waste to chumps nonstop
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like they heard somebody over here was handing out asses and theyve known nothing but years of bitter ass famine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like they heard somebody over here was handing out asses and theyve known nothing but years of bitter ass famine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like they heard somebody over here was handing out asses and theyve known nothing but years of bitter ass famine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like they heard somebody over here was handing out asses and theyve known nothing but years of bitter ass famine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: noirs outta control
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: rose is crazy jades crazier and youre
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well youre you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and together were up to our bulges and miscellaneous bullshit alien physiology in hot sloppy shenanigans 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: while hatching plans under our feathery asses like a bunch of cage free farm fresh motherfuckers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but im not about to get into specifics cause this is complicated enough as it is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: id start sounding like one of these smug alternian shitheads and im not about to drop that retarded science on my good bro
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: give me your money
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im working the system here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: using time loops to manipulate the incipispheres financial sector
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: making a goddamn killing in the lohacse
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lohac stock exchange
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: land of heat and clockwork dude come on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you know like gears and lava and shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wrong it kicks ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: egbert stfu and give me your goddamn boonbuck j3gus fuck
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill turn it into a boonmint in an hour and youll get it back ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no comment
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you can wire it to my account
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont do the vriska thing ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh shit really
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that loud sound of shock you just smelled was my jaw hitting the floor
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant possibly argue with any of that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so are we done making money yet or what
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like a hungry beggar loitering cross the street of an olive garden
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just cause a filthy vagrants barred from entry dont mean a dude doesnt know italian foods nearby its a fucking fact to his nose
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: does that get to be not an obnoxious secret yet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alright well its not like i even have a problem parting with this useless bullshit money
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: how bout i give you an even boonbank
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why werent we just wiring money into the past for these investment escapades instead of doing all this time traveling
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuckin aliens
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: brace yourself six hours ago
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes im a girl
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: north american hollering phallus baboon
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: when our territory is threatened thats when the indiscriminate fucking begins
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: could fuck a circus tent down a gas tank
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: beep beep albino hairless dickmonkey coming through
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the glittering civilization before you was built on angry apefuck power alone
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stand agog and marvel bitch
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shaggy 2 dope
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its ben stiller
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh man another failed trolling attempt
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: excuse me but it says right in the header of this conversation that youre trolling me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: excuse me but it says right in the header of this conversation that youre trolling me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: excuse me but it says right in the header of this conversation that youre trolling me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: let me just set aside some time to be stupid enough to believe that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey looks like next month is chemical lobotomy month youre in luck
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: borderline pornographic
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: need to figure out my own ironic statement to make
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pretty deep troll girl
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that fucking puppet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my fucking hell
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that is horrendous
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a fucking pork chop
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so overwhelmed i cant even damn type
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats a retarded thing to say even by the standard of your own bullshit made up vernacular
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok asking for an explanation on that is pretty much the exact opposite of what im doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and interesteds the opposite of what im being
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok that remark was almost as boring as it was weird
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont cry
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i plan on forgetting about you instantly after this conversation
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill just forget on principle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pretty cool guy here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: case you hadnt noticed 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the fuck was the point of this again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this was a setup all along
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if you say i warned you about tears or something one more time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: our memes can cancel each other out this time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its the fucking onions
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: these piece of shit crocodiles are lambasting me with them
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess the stench of onions is covering up the smell of the truth how convenient
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also your nose sux youre not even any good at smellin at all
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the only thing im getting is out of this goddamn idiot cauldron here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the only thing im going to make is like banana and split
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: out of this bubbling pail of misery
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: tell me its more alien nonsense it will be so awesome to hear more of that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why did i ever agree to go along with this horseshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: they dont have any secrets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the only secret theyve got is how many times a day they accidentally flush their medical alert bracelets down the toilet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok im gonna change out of this wet suit and into a dry shut your fucking mouth 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i smell like a coal miners asshole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess i forgot i was supposed to forget
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the hell
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whats your obsession with making this goofy bullshit anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is it troll irony
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh fuck there i am hiding behind that column
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but whats the answer that doesnt have anything to do with meaningless bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ...........
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like watching a miracle made of nothing but twitching schroder legs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: those moves
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i can see im going to have to drop everything
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: drop it like its simultaneously hot and i just tripped over the rug
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dedicate my undivided attention to this shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: truth be told everyone will be tripping when im done
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: once i upset this biznasty with my swift cuts
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dudes will phalanx themselves agape like theyre offerin to store my shit in their mouths for the night
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: rows of glasseyed human fly catchers beholding categorical fucking domination of the dance floor
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but they wont catch none cause the flys all mine
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im crafting a new dance move to shock the shit out of asses in pants
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fred astaires ghost will weep in the arms of his own nimble rotting corpse
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the smug cracker parlor wiggle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and just when the scene thought it was startin to recover from its ridiculous erection over that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats when i bust out another fierce move
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i call it rageclock me in the douche smirk plz
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cut out to the rude jam "askin 4 it!"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: id say if i had to take an educated guess it was outright goddamn unmannerly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: needs to get worked over by some stuffy prude at finishing school
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont know if you can keep up with me kid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no offense
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theres just magic in these shoes and the coy gnome i ransacked wants them goddamn back
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i feel like i should be offering some visual rebuttal here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i keep forgetting i can time travel
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok could you try to be somehow even less subtle when you hit on me thanks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im going to infer that your species reproduces by having sex with a grub in a bucket or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: huh what an odd thing to say
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it demands no explanation whatsoever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok after all this hype you better be prepared to fucking dazzle me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: luring me into your cyber boobytrap with shitty clip art who told you my weakness
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: some kinda asshole rumpus looks like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but what else is new just another lady from outer space mackin on me whatever chance she gets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john god dammit stop embarrassing us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: first of all weve got to be on record here as not giving a shit about that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: second obviously theres gonna be 4 quadrants come on 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sounds like a loudmouth inferiority thing going on here to me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like you dont want to acknowledge that your troll ladies find a couple of human dudes irresistible
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: would you want to ask her to go see one of your dumbass movies
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like the new maconnohey jam where he smirks and like all but deliberately draws the audiences ire like a goddamn magnetron 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: holding a bucket full of flowers or slime or whatever and jade was like no thanks bro
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: john just a heads up in the future i think youre gonna spurn one of his awkward advances
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my fucking god
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: please let this conversation not be taking place
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok youre by far the worst artist out of any of us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thx for the shipping grid bro imma drop everything and go have a baby with jade right now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it was so much cooler when you were asleep and i basically never had to listen to you ever 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you were the best troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in the most ironic and hilarious ways possible
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you did your bizarrely oblivious juggalo thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and we both proceeded to have one of the best rap-offs in the history of paradox space
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youll finally figure out who you are and why you worship all this ridiculous clown bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and also why your planet has faygo for some baffling reason
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: actually no nevermind it doesnt explain that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that still makes no damn sense
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: your dark clownish salvation or whatever the fuck
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: your mirthful messiahs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahaha i cant even type that without lmao
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: on earth class is sorted out by who can drop the most delirious flow 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: rap battles
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the kings of wordtech ascend to godhood and look down on us patriarchally like urban watermarks in the sky
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: til the rapocalypse happened
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: subwoofing out devotion every which way
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: was foretold hed come after meteors show up to drop it like its hot
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and hed gather up the ashes of our civilization and lift it like its heavy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuck im tearing up my ishades are gonna fry 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: douche
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if youre gonna spit that kind of bravado at me im just saying put it in rhyme
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets hear what you got tooly mcsnoothole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that brorage lust youre feelin
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: turn that bitch inside out like a broke ass millionaires pockets 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: weird but alright
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hes paradoxically me but richer and surlier
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: worth more than all the chests lockpicked and gold croc bricks and boonbucks i pickpocketed
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fillin folios with millions im milkin to pad out my pockets
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: which i posit you got shit of that nature in spades
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: spyin a guy whos eyed more cocks and dicks than i got clocks and they got ticks 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok hold that thought im gonna pull this fuckin sword out of the thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: holy shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the fuck 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok maybe youre actually the worst troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im thinking none of that was actually ironic that was all pretty straightup wasnt it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuckin piece of shit sword
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wont goddamn budge probably useless anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a legendary piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a legendary piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a legendary piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a legendary piece of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you mean the guy who spent years beating my ass down with a puppet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just cause i broke a cheap ass sword doesnt make me the fucking hulk
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: god everything is about parties with you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets see some fine art then
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is every bit as shitty as all your other drawings
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: art skills are overrated
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its kind of weird though what the hell is actually going on here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean even if that made sense which it kind of doesnt
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: to piss him off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my grill is your goddamn prison
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you are practically incarcerated in that fucker
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: doing hard time on a bed of charcoal and lighterfluid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: privy to what i flame broil from below
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what im sayin is you got a front row seat to the brown side of my burger
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is this some weird game involving flirtation and assassinations or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats pretty much the most insulting thing possible to say im anything like that raving gulf of shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey look at this change of subject going down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bonkin me with yarn or some shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre gonna miss a hell of a show
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what are welsh things doing in this game
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats an awesome question
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is this thing as pointless as i think it is or do i need it for something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuck it ill just power through the rest of the game with the SORD.....
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with unreal air as a mount fit for a true artifact knight
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: goddamn jpeg hero
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thrashing ill grinds on clouds
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats an order from your celestial fuckin spirit guide
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: volcano
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yup
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theres all sorts of stuff i suddenly knew about the game when i became this orange feathery asshole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a wise feathery asshole
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am fuckin filthy with wisdom its sick
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its all good
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all tangled up in ridiculous riddles and bullshit enigmas
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anyway monsters will show up soon and try to eat my sleeping corpse
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah they werent too happy with my reckless indiana jones bullshit either
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: guess ill make myself comfortable here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: up away to the sun like a fucknig piece of gargbage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: caw caw motherfuckers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: caw caw motherfuckers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: caw caw motherfuckers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: caw caw motherfuckers
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats just perfect hahahaha 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nak nak nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nak nak nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nak nak nak nak nak nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nak nak nak nak nak nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nak nak nak nak nak nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nakka nakka nak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: MY GLASSES ARE TALKING TO ME MY GLASSES ARE TALKING TO ME
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: MY GLASSES ARE TALKING TO ME MY GLASSES ARE TALKING TO ME
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: naknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknak 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: naknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknak 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: naknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknak 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lavas better
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: snows a big chilly carpet of nobody gives a shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like old man winter spread around his nasty mayonnaise and turned the landscape into his personal asshole sandwich
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: when i look around all i see is the miles of unharnessed snowmen im just too damn cool to build
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whoa jade with the fucking haymaker
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i need to go look for my teeth on the canvas as soon as shit stops spinning and there stops being like ten of you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: time then shades
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: time//shades lets go
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im not gonna play in the snow
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe you missed those credentials i flashed which clearly stated me being too cool for that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like federally too cool
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my coolness is named after a dead president plus his middle initial to make it sound extra legit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: blew up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i completely understand everything about that practically entirely
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wind mission or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: getting all his ridiculous magic cyclone powers on and realizing his huge blowy destiny
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: as the chump of shoosh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: remember how i was scrambling up that tower to get that egg like an idiot
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the hell was i doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i was like goddamn pooh bear in a tree reaching up his fat fuckin pooh paw for some mother fuckin honey
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so even though im awesome now at one point i was plausibly likened to an autistic stuffed animal
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you told me how it worked all christopher robinning my ignorant ass about that egg
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but i was all like IM A LITTLE BLACK RAIN CLOUD BITCH WATCH ME CLIMB
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: deploy the intellibeam laserstation
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its mostly pretty stupid and useless
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats why this is so dumb
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so the solution to the anti piracy measure is to override the anti spam measure
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cause god knows the last thing youd want was some web bot being able to figure out the code for like a potted plant
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that would be fucking mayhem
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but in order to effectively cheat here weve got to open pandoras spam box
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and release the laserstation into the world with its leering intellibeam
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: now no captcha is safe youll have bots signing up for email accounts and duplicating potted plants and shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: basically robots are in control now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the bad news is theyre all pornbots and theyve got LOADS of provocative material theyre just dying to share with us
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: THE GLASSES ARE TALKING AGAIN
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: naknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknaknak
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: :V
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: :(
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and kind of boring
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: being all creepy and dream duplicitous and shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all your books are bizarre and terrible
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it was like peering through the dark portal of an eldritch red lobster and scoping out its all you can eat seafood buffet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: went and perved up some sleeping girls room to take my mind of it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im not about to get molested by calamari with fucking teeth
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stroke a mummys paw or some horseshit and open a dark channel
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: tell them to keep their lecherous flagella to themselves
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh shit youre kidding
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no really are you serious i didnt even notice
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuck mind = blown 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a treasure map 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: or bigger
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see how important that contextualization was now i know how fucking impressed i should be
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean hopy shit thats huge
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: with the help of a million rambunctious gross tentacle mutants
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: blast off to adventure 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: jesus can we stop with the fancy colored text bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sounds like a really credible dude sign me up for trusting everything he says
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: those fuckers are all kinds of mad expendable
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: way to leave me hanging there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is going to be fucking stupid isnt it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dog it as long as possible
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its blossoming into an interspecies partnership in incredibly shitty cartooning
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fuckin trolls too many of them who can even keep track of this shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is it the absurd juggalo one that would be hilarious 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well im suddenly not interested so go talk to your fairy god troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill be over here paving the way for your elaborate dream suicide
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its lame for you to pretend theres any element of suspense here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes how would it ever stop being a thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: being a things not something it ever stopped doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: before i decide to start choppin off the heads of outrageously good looking snoozing dudes 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: does this mean later im going to have to put this ugly goddamn suit back on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: if we make mistakes then dead daves start piling up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and dead daves are the enemy remember
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i probably would have gone back in time and killed my own grandfather oh wait i never had one 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: twoface is a human batman villain whos half ugly and flips coins all the time to make evil decisions 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its ok flippin coins for reasons is still pretty badass i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh ok its someone who asks a bunch of dumb riddles i figured it out already
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets not get derailed here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this whole thing was a ruse
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you could smell a flea off a dogs balls 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i know it biblically its an obscene nsfw spectacle 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it turned into schrodingers fucking dave 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok im going to torrent you another like negative billion artifact grists
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: now draw the conksuckiest boot you ever drew 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its the conksuckiest piece of fucking shit that ever still somehow qualified as a boot
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this is some pretty serious existence threatening shit going down and some people are going to die i guess
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: even crazy hard dudes like my bro slash weird covert biological ghost dad 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: bottom line is were all related slimewise except you and me and him and rose pairways respectively
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: makes the shipping chart pretty simple here hang on while i dig up that piece of shit karkat made
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just imagine something ugly made by a jackass 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fightin off wave after wave of face pumicing puppet ass every day
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: always being on guard for stealth attacks in the middle of the night while getting up to go to the fucking bathroom
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but im still trapped in the chronologistics of this fuckin one man ballet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youre a fan of one of my websites arent you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what asshole gave you my chumhandle
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: also what was your favorite thing i did you liked
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: asl??? 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh holy shit ok youre a troll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: makes no sense bye 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: cool story 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok so 2=6 awesome joke hahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im gonna shut off my phone now cya 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: looks like youre a fairy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lucky bastard
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is reality still a thing that means something can that be a question on the table too 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i pictured a lot more mayhem like
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a bunch of trolls flying around in little grub pods constantly screaming at each other through bullhorns shaped like buckets 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what is like the primary activity here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that ghosts get their shit worked up over
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are those sick fires youre packing there
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you best not be bringin that fire into my bubble less you plan on dropping that shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am your general fucking practitioner and doctors orders are to shut up and burn down my goddamn office
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill break your brittle ass like a graham cracker and well roast smores over the flaming debris have i made myself clear 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: gross
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its my eternal punishment to have shitty rapoffs with this tool forever is that it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: were just forfeiting all rhyme or reason to this unmitigated clusterfuck is that it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: puppets arent cool theyre shitty small fake people who haunt your dreams and grin like permanent assholes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: a guy can be sad and make jokes at the same time 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i am grieving to the max like a widow on dead husband island
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: behind these chill as fuck shades my face is having this crazy attack of the sads
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my rue is fucking bananas cant you tell 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the truth is a mystery tucked behind the pursed lips of a shitty riddler
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: they will be loosened only when presented with the conundrous grandeur of rigid insoluble puzzlecock
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sorry you are so flustered by the mere mention of glittering mythical cryptodick it honestly makes me think youre not ready for the truth 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: filthiest thing you ever said
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pulling swords out of things isnt how i roll
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: pretty much nothing but horsing around through time and swindling retarded alligators out of their life savings
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im a lie my ass right down here for a while looking slightly less cool than i make myself out to be ordinarily 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you havent heard me bleat like a goat for ironically humorous purposes yet have you 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that was something that was mentioned at some point by someone i forget when or why
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i bet you are on goddamn pins and needles waiting for that arent you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that sure sounds like a dumb way to say a thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: almost egbertian in elegant stupidity
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the t in egbertian is soft like shhhhh 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so completely illegal
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why did i just say that stupid thing i said
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok that came out wrong
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what were we talking about again
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: slammer means jail
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you call it the slammer when youre extra angry at crimes
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: are you taking notes on this important principle?? jesus get a fucking pen
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: holy shit why do i care about THAT suddenly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: anyway thats more shit that popped into my head just now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i need to shut up now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im sounding like an idiot and my head is starting to hurt
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok i cant even make little interrogative quips to grease the wheels of your monologue 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: spidertroll 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hunt me down and lawyerviscerate me for my own good 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lame motion overruled the judge wants to see where this is going 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i thought you were insane kinds of apeshit over the macabre stuff
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this huge fuckin whopper im about to just say 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok first do you even have burger kings out in the fucking woods
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why do you reference things that obviously arent in the woods like terrible burgers 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean it was a doozy like psychologically speaking
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: doozy is a slightly dumber word than whopper
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like whatever tangy sludge the king himself squirts on his bargain patties
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its possible that i dreamt it ironically i dunno
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: every bit as thick and juicy as a half pound of sizzling grade A premium ok this is stupid weve got to get burgers out of this conversation
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its grotesquely pregnant with meaning
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: all gestating at least 8 gooey octuplets thrashing around in an undulating belly full of mind slime 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just want your professional take on how many things in my dream symbolize dicks 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah thats a given but i didnt even dream about puppets this time 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: god this is so generically morbid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im sorry in advance for exposing you to my unconscious minds retarded cliches 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: well obviously i knew the birds were just black screaming sky dongs just hear me out
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you mean maybe its about anxiety over maintaining my blogs
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we both know theyre fresher than your moms change of drawers and tighter than when shes wearin them 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i can visualize her choice ass all i want without it gettin much more than moderately uncomfortable for everyone involved 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so i flapped my wings and flew up away to it like a fucking piece of garbage
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: not in the sense that it was a dark sacrificial zoology mission
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then the cage bunny came
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dumb 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its manboobs are jiggling a little 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey were gonna hunt frogs til you shoot me through the jack
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: then i die and youve got to make out with me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this conversation just got bumrushed by a mudslide of fucking awful 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes ima authorize a GOD DAMN you may swipe it at the door to check yourself into the burn ward 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nah those are kept in emergency reserve for yo mama jokes from the 90s
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe id rather just be like the dave of guy
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you know just some dude 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes those exact bitches 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it still cuts like its plowing through a shaft of boneless zombie meat 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: heres how bad this is
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: were are basically bruce willis and ben affleck from johns shitty crappy movie
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you made this even more armageddon than it already was
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sealing me in the air lock so i can go home to liv tyler and have the most terrible babies with her 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the bunny or the actress 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this probably comes close but that doesnt make it not lame as hell 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its cool you are so tickled by this i hope it brought you a lot of rad laughs on your way to go fucking explode
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and now youre dead and im dream chilling with your smug ghost
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i turned into a bird and got in a fight 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shenanigans mostly 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the fuckin welsh sword dave broke
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: just before going into a major league wind up with your nap yarn 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no one likes a basketball hog 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in the athletic arena of competitive achievement
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a widely known fact that cherry picking posers get showered in nothin but boos
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont gank the rock and steal the big mans thunder on his raucus drive to the hole 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is that the sort of ignominy you want
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: see you didnt consider sports you never consider the sports 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it like the tight end was going long down the yard in sudden death
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its me im the tight end
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and the quarterback sniped the fieldgoal just before the nfl buzzer went off
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but instead of winning the gold sports prize you just fucking die and nobody cares and it didnt mean anything 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the football prize 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its called the bruce bombardi trophy or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for best pile squad 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and even though youre dead all these fat millionaires in helmets just leap on your corpse anyway and pile up and i mean WAY up 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the sport pile doesnt stop from getting taller 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yes poser it should be my torso getting pulverized by that avalanche of overpaid beefcakes and you know it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: there obviously stopped being a difference between those things the question is offensive
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: almost as offensive as you stalling me while you peel out of here in your dumb moon 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: whos this douche dag
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i always forget i can talk underlined for important shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so he looked me up and down all hard
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: meh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: because of ascending to doghood 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this icp shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lame clown rap and stuff 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude are you an actual juggalo or not 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant even tell if youre trying to troll me with this or if you actually are having some weird emotional problem 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: none of that really meant anything but ok
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: did my bro put you up to this
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i should have guessed he might have a hand in some of these shitty trolling escapades 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: my bros idiotic ventriloquist dummy is responsible for this schizophrenic bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: welp
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: time to block you now but lets do this again ok 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: maybe ill humorously defile willis and afflecks dumb skyward yearning faces 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: come on dude hand it over 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: too late i already did it with sprite powers while he wasnt looking 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ahahahaha you fucked up
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh my god we are never going to stop fucking with each other are we
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean i think even a civilization full of the laziest sons of bitches are gonna make up a myth figure for death
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i basically have no fucking imagination that sounds badass to me
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: lets go ahead stick that in our culture forever 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude chill out we just got hornswoggled is all 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: man what the hell even happened on this meteor anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i got sicknasty logistics up my sleeve
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i just call them stics fyi which is how you know im way savvy about them
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: most of the stics im fine tuning atm involve rap though i should warn you
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but dave what if that dope as hell plan falls through i can hear you ask
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: plan b involves drawing some shitty cartoons and not giving a fuck about stuff 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: rose i told you this dude is fucking incredible 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait has the juggalo troll been giving you guys fits like this or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean like personal tragedies notwithstanding 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: he made this stupid leather bib for me out of a goddamn horse
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for the ironies obviously 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats a hell of a mystery no one thought was a mystery and didnt even really need solving
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what is he the mayor of anyway
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it kinda looks like he just made that sash himself 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: talk about an elusive juggalo
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: probably like the shyest fuckin juggalo of all time
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont expect him to rat him out either because of the "morail" junk
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: mwah rail...
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: alien words 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i mean i bet you think youre imparting some really obscure cultural fact about trolls
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: "hey man can you tell me where your best clown friend is hiding so i can go chainsaw him to death"
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is she trying to be his kismet fish 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fu
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nobodys mistaking that about me im a time traveler not a fuckin fortune teller its simple as shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nice 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nice 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nice 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: nice 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok i didnt really catch any of that bullshit cause i wasnt listening
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im gonna make myself a cup of coffee and get primed to listen to you saying a lot of stuff like that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this fuckin thing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: where did you even unearth this piece of shit from
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: two hot revitalizing cups of shitty coffee
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fresh out of the weird pod
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why do we even drink this shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wish there was such a thing as apple juice on troll world
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: could go for a bottle of aj
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i wonder if theres any booze squirreled away on this meteor
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kinda feels like we should be drinking our asses off here
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: wait what the fuck am i saying trolls dont even have adults
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but theyre all in outer space being insane badasses
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i guess they do have the stupid nanny monsters
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do the monsters give a shit if they get wasted 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: off the shit is how
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: in cups and everything 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is that more wizard fan fiction 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ok totally sold on that suddenly
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: on account of not caring
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and we sit back and wait for it to do its huge ribbit or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dunno if im ready to process the ramifications of this bullshit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ive been fuck deep in alt daves before
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a goddamn delight if you want to know the truth
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: but your mom was just a nice alcoholic spinster who liked wizards who you complained about for no reason
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: let me ask you this did your mom ever wiggle a puppet in your face even ONCE
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: fine well you can be on bro duty then
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill be the ambassador to your mom
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: and no that wasnt actually meant as the sick burn it sounded like 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill be the ambassador to my mom then
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that sounds pretty stupid when i say it that way
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ill be the fuckin one man welcome wagon for the john and jade teen old people and also our mom thats the plan
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: so when we finally see them we can get our shit into formation like trained acrobats
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: like ill blow a whistle and we make a human pyramid got it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that way we can totally avoid anything awkward 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we both know that was a lot of horseplay bullfuckery between like smartass 10 year olds or whatever
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: ugh dont ever do that
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: momtraps and sistertraps
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its like a huge blue perv thats mad jazzed for kidcest 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dont you wink at her
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: kanaya heres a protip that wink meant jack dick shes just being weird 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: yeah im pretty much ollying outie too
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: karkat is broken guys 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hey dont be saying shit about the mayor
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: the mayor rules hes like my best fucking friend 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hes a mayor you douche his thing says mayor 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no mayo is like grub sauce but without grubs 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dunno its white and it just sort of exists
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dont ask about mayo thats not what you do with mayo 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what did you actually sprint all the way across the meteor to tell me this 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: dude dont touch my cape
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant believe i seriously just said dude dont touch my cape to somebody and was serious about it
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: havent you only watched a bunch of shitty dane cook movies on infinite loop since we left 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you know youre only pretending to be a huge fan of his bullshit to piss me off 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hrnngngnngghhhh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: it turns out that exact sentence is my one weakness
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what the hot mess of fresh fuck am i looking at 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you lost me at quadrant
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: for future reference thats the word that always lets me know its time to check out of a sentence 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: n drangles
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what is that huge beefcake troll even doing
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: is he grinding against the little dudes shoulder what is even going on
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why the fuck is he nude 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im not reading that shit
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: there is nothing even slightly applicable about any of that bullshit to our situation 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why is this happening 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: youve completely lost it dude
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i cant believe for a fucking second this is reasonable shit to propose even on troll world
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hnnrrghh
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: no you are NOT making another shipping grid dude 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: its a grid youre drawing a goddamn grid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: im not letting you draw a grid for this stupid shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: put the fucking pen down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do not draw a shipping grid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do not do it 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you are not drawing a grid to organize our goddamn dating lives
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that is some straight up crackpot motherfuckin noise i will not abide 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stop drawing the shipping grid 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you will not draw anything that even remotely resembles a grid
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do not draw an arrangement of squares or otherwise interlocking polygons 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you will not draw a spreadsheet for the purpose of allocating time spent with a mutual girlfriend you horses ass
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that is exactly the shit i do not want to see 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do not draw any additional squares
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: do not draw any quadrilaterals or trapezoids or rectangles or fucking n-drangles and especially as fuck not any god damned rhombuses
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: i dont want to see your lines making any right angles do you understand 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: that is the perfect example of what you shouldnt be drawing 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: put the goddamn pen down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you piece of shit 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: splitting up her time in a grid for your stupid rotating hate date plan
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: what a presumptuous sack of shit put the pen down
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: step away from your dumb ugly scribble grid.
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you are the fuckin big man of smellin bad
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you dominate the paint with your stonk 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you smell like if someone took a dump on a butt 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theyre magic fucking pajamas they stay like perma clean or something
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: theyre enchanted and comfy as fuck give me the pen 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: why are you drawing all these human dicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this book is now like our fight fueled ouija board of cock 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this book is now like our fight fueled ouija board of cock 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: this book is now like our fight fueled ouija board of cock 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the spooky thing about penis ouija you can never be sure who did the dicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the spooky thing about penis ouija you can never be sure who did the dicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the spooky thing about penis ouija you can never be sure who did the dicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: thats the spooky thing about penis ouija you can never be sure who did the dicks
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: was it you or me or maybe a ghoooost??? 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: was it you or me or maybe a ghoooost??? 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: was it you or me or maybe a ghoooost??? 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we are in the shit now
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: we are motherfuckin entrenched in this bitch 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: shut up and draw another penis 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: stop biting my cape 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: you are like a cape magnet
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: hup
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: BOOYEAH
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (mayor what do you think)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (the mayor thinks its an awesome idea)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (me too buddy me too) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (what the fuck kind of question is that)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (i am the fucking yarn king)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (be passin out yarn like cheap cigars) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (dream mom gave teen ecto birth or some shit)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (turned out the baby was us)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (are you still magic or is your superpower now just talking a lot and wearing orange)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (like are spells real like when you do magic are you actualy doing legit spells like the dipshits in harry potter)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (babbling up some false baloney ass latin) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (i knew it what a load of shit that all is) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (spells and shit) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (can a dream self be drunk) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (oh god i never get used to how quietly troll vampires sneak around) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (liquor is booze you drink it and it makes you fall down and slur words and understand sports)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (and apparently snore like an off road motorcycle) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (yeah we know fucking squat)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (maybe we should have been paying attention i dont even know what the hell these people are talking about)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (this is awkward)
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: (she is like literally the only one on the ball here this is embarrassing) 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: oh shit grandpa egbert juniordad totally snapped 
@dave_idle%alttextbox_twitter DAVE/_EBUBBLES: juggalos
				</args>
			</action>
</classes>
</sburb>
