<sburb><classes>
<action class='araneaDialog1' name='Talk to Aranea.' command='talk'><args>
      @aranea_happier ARANEA: There you are! 
      @aranea_happy:#Everyone-has-missed-you! ARANEA: Haven't seen much of you since you joined us in the afterlife. I know you are "royalty" and all, 8ut it isn't very socia8le of you to lock yourself in your lavish moon hive forever.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: well im here now arent i
      @aranea_talk:#Wordplay#8-letter-words#Oh-yes ARANEA: Yes. And it's good thing you are. I was just a8out to come find you, so we could discuss the recent... Calamity. Out in the a8yss.
      @meenah_creepytalk:#splosions MEENAH: yeah!!! so you saw it too huh
      @meenah_happytalk:#skull-guy#laser-breath MEENAH: that was the guy right
      @meenah_idle:#uh MEENAH: lord somefin
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: clamiborn? whatd you say his shit was again
      @aranea_annoyedtalk:#8ad-juju ARANEA: I'd try to avoid saying his true name.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: whats it matter
      @meenah_talk:#heheh MEENAH: hes already here aint he
      @aranea_madtalk:#Ghost-murder#Second-death#Soulicide ARANEA: I guess. 8ut yes, the Lord of Time was responsi8le for the destruction of that dream 8u88le, and the murder of all those innocent ghosts.
      @meenah_idle:#... MEENAH: innocent ghosts
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#dumb MEENAH: killin ghosts as a thing that can happen is seriously the dumbest shit i ever heard 
      @aranea_happytalk:#Like-you ARANEA: I don't make the rules, Meenah. I merely o8serve them, and explain them thoroughly to anyone who will listen.
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: yeah 
      @meenah_talk:#fishpuns#2xcombo#booyeah MEENAH: last thing i need is anemonemore of your lobstervations
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: anyway that explosion kicked ass
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#like-school-of-fishes-i-mean#38D#38D#38D MEENAH: splosions rule the school!!! 38D 
      @aranea_talk:#Um........ ARANEA: I agree that it's more excitement than we've seen here for millenia. 8ut all of us here in the afterlife are in serious danger of 8eing extermin8ed!!!!!!!!
      @aranea_think:#!!!!!!!! ARANEA: Again.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yeah i got that
      @meenah_happytalk:#this-time-i-might-not-even-blow-yall-up-w-a-bomb MEENAH: i figured id have to be the heroe and bail you suckas out again
      @aranea_surprised ARANEA: Oh really?
      @aranea_happier:#I'm-very-curious! ARANEA: What exactly is your plan?
      @meenah_angrytalk:#duh MEENAH: to get all us ghosts here to team up and kill that asshole
      @aranea_angry ARANEA: What!
      @aranea_facepalmtalk:#Poor-death-choices ARANEA: Oh, Meenah. That is such a terri8le idea.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yeah right
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: like you have a better idea
      @aranea_happy ARANEA: As a matter of fact, I do! ::::)
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='araneaDialog2' name='Ask about friends.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_talk:#dead-fronds#ghostbros#haunt-pals#idk MEENAH: so where is everymoby i wanna talk to them bout somefin
      @aranea_talk ARANEA: I 8elieve most of our friends have gathered in this dream 8u88le.
      @aranea_think ARANEA: You should 8e a8le to find them if you explore a 8it.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: What do you want to talk to them a8out?
      @meenah_creepy:#alpha-troll-reunion-yo MEENAH: gotta get the gang back together
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: take down the douche of time
      @meenah_happytalk:#losers#losing-experts#lossmasters#failpros MEENAH: you say hes invincible but i think thats exactly the kind of loser bs that made us lose like a bunch of fuckin losers in the first losin place
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: we can do it if we all like
      @meenah_wut:#teamfork#lol MEENAH: work together and shit
      @meenah_happy:#or-maybe... MEENAH: if we build an army
      @meenah_happier MEENAH: a G)(OST army 38D
      @meenah_ohyes:#so-sick MEENAH: think a how glubbin sick would that be
      @aranea_madtalk ARANEA: Sick, perhaps. 8ut not a very good strategy!
      @aranea_annoyedtalk ARANEA: You will just 8e leading everyone into permanent o8livion. At least you will without coming up with a 8etter plan first.
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: then whats your awesome idea
      @aranea_happy:#Patience#Peixes#Alliterative-assonance ARANEA: To 8e a little more patient. 
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: I have 8een following clues regarding the wherea8outs of a secret weapon that may 8e the key to defeating him. 
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: oh reely
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: whats the weaprawn
      @aranea_annoyedtalk:#Weaprawn?#Really,-Meenah? ARANEA: The weaprawn........ weapon, I mean, is not a what, 8ut a who.
      @aranea_happytalk:#Aliens ARANEA: She is the other cheru8. The Lord's female counterpart, who once occupied the same 8ody.
      @aranea_talk:#Xeno8iologically-fascinating-species ARANEA: 8ut when they reached maturity, his personality dominated the host, assuming complete control. 
      @aranea_talk:#Or-so-the-legend-goes ARANEA: She technically died that day, and now her spirit presuma8ly roams somewhere out here in the Furthest Ring.
      @aranea_madtalk ARANEA: We need to find her 8efore he does. He will surely want to finish her off.
      @meenah_annoyed:#uh MEENAH: cherub
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: what
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: ok i didnt really follow any of that junk so uh
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: you go right ahead and find your cherub girl
      @meenah_creepytalk:#ghost-army#beeyotch#fyeah MEENAH: ima be right here building my ghost army B--E-EYOTC)(
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Very well. 8est of luck with that!
      @aranea_talk:#Like,-almost-eternity ARANEA: 8ut try to remem8er it has 8een a very long time since any of our friends have done anything important at all.
      @aranea_talk:#I-hope-you-like-frustrating-conversations ARANEA: It may 8e more difficult to find recruits for your army than you think.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: please
      @meenah_talk:#chumps#shame-globes#chumpiness#globage MEENAH: ok i admit that mosta them were chumpy as globes when we was tryin to win our game
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: but this time when im through with em they will be the loyal murderous mob of cherubfucking fury our people were always supposed to be
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#batterwitch#waterbitch#omfg#yes#yes#yes#yes MEENAH: and if you dont think i can do that then N-E-ED I R-EMIND YOU who i grew up to be in some another dimension or whatever
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: You needn't remind me at all, Your Condescension.
      @aranea_happy:#::::) ARANEA: I 8elieve you were hatched to 8e a tyrant, and I pray that your campaign of 8ullying and intimidation goes swimmingly. 
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: aw youre tha best serket cmere 38*
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='roseDialog1' name='Talk to Rose.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: hey!!!!
      @rose_idle ROSE: Hello.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: its uh
      @meenah_happier MEENAH: YOU
      @rose_idle ROSE: Yes.
      @meenah_wut:#where-da-horns-at#so-weird MEENAH: human right
      @rose_talk ROSE: That's right.
      @rose_talk ROSE: Rose, more specifically.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: who cares listen human girl wanna ask ya somefin
      @rose_concern ROSE: You're not very good at this, are you?
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: wut
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: Talking to people.
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: hey eff you
      @rose_happytalk:#I-can-kind-of-relate,-actually. ROSE: It's ok that you are. I'm not trying to criticize.
      @rose_concern:#Beforan-moon ROSE: I've heard some things about you. That pink rocky environment back there. That's a memory of your home, right?
      @meenah_annoyed:#... MEENAH: 
      @rose_talk ROSE: You renounced the throne and ran away to the moon, didn't you? And then you lived there completely alone for... how many years?
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: what are years
      @rose_happytalk:#Abyss-madness#Meteor-fever ROSE: I think I'm starting to lose track of what a year is myself. That seems to be what happens when you spend enough time out here.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: uh
      @rose_coytalk:#Also,-I-like-your-braids. ROSE: I'm just curious about you. You seem like an interesting person who probably has a lot of stories to tell.
      @rose_concern ROSE: From what I understand, you discovered something on the moon which originally contained your copy of the game? Is that true?
      @meenah_idle:#dot#dot#dot MEENAH: ...
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Maybe we could spend some time together and get to know each other? When you have the chance, of course.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: man
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: youre like an alien windfang
      @meenah_talk:#altpun-=#discernabubble MEENAH: all wordy and nosy and nice to me for no fishcernible reason
      @meenah_happytalk:#goddamn-ugly MEENAH: you even have the same cod tier jammies on
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#fuchsia-blows-orange-out-of-the-water MEENAH: just another bright orange blubbermouth
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: lets just forget i said anyfin kay
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='roseDialog2' name='Ask Rose to join.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: sooooo
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: extra talky human
      @meenah_happytalk:#suuup MEENAH: its me again
      @rose_happy:#:) ROSE: Hey!
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: got a porpoisition for ya
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you know that bad guy
      @meenah_happytalk:#rainbow-barfer MEENAH: just wrecked the sky and killed some dead mofos
      @rose_annoyed ROSE: Lord English?
      @rose_sad ROSE: Yes, I know of him.
      @meenah_creepytalk MEENAH: wanna team up with me and kill him or...
      @rose_idle ROSE: Absolutely.
      @meenah_happier:#word MEENAH: yay!!!! 38D
      @rose_happy:#Much-later,-really. ROSE: But later. 
      @meenah_wut2:#ugh MEENAH: gfd
      @rose_talk:#Troll-Isaac-Newton ROSE: We can't interrupt the plan which has been put into inexorable motion. Or for that matter, the meteor we're traveling on, which has been similarly propelled.
      @rose_talk:#Alpha-players#Teen-guardians#Fun ROSE: We have to rendezvous with our rebooted "ancestors," as it were, and help them win their game.
      @rose_happytalk:#Additional-fun ROSE: In the process, we will ideally become stronger and more experienced. Only then will we be ready to help you defeat him.
      @meenah_talk:#blahblahblahblahblah MEENAH: oh my glub you really are serketting the fuck outta this
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: come on stop overplanning lets all just fly away together and wreck his shit
      @meenah_happytalk:#BILLIONS#i-mean#probably MEENAH: there are like billions a ghosts out here right we got numbers on our side
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: Yes. But even if I agreed, I couldn't just fly away with you now.
      @rose_concern:#Kind-of-like-a-hologram,-I-guess? ROSE: I'm not even standing here. I'm asleep on our meteor. This is a dream projection you're talking to.
      @meenah_annoyed:#wut MEENAH: wut
      @rose_laugh ROSE: You're new to dream bubbles, aren't you.
      @rose_coytalk ROSE: I would be more than happy to explain to you how they work in extensive detail.
      @meenah_angry MEENAH: ugh
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: LIG)(T PLAY-ERS
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: later rosefang
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='kanayaDialog1' name='Talk to Kanaya.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: oh hey the maryam looking girl
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: what is the deal with you
      @kanaya_bored:#The-Deal-With-Things#The-Topic-Of-Wonder#People-Looking-People KANAYA: The Deal With The Maryam Looking Girl Is That She Is Wondering What The Deal Is With The Peixes Looking Girl And Specifically Why The Former Has Piqued The Latters Curiosity
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: why
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: dunno
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#i-mean#two-captors-id-undersand MEENAH: seams to me two maryams is overdoin it a bit
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: one was more than enough 
      @kanaya_smirktalk KANAYA: The Same Thing Occurred To Me
      @meenah_talk:#u-talk-weird MEENAH: you arent much like the one we had
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: kind of a tough act to follow to be fair though
       @kanaya_facepalm:#Things-That-Are-The-Same#And-How-They-Occur-To-People KANAYA: The Same Thing Occurred To Me Yet Again
      @meenah_happytalk:#damn#ur-blindin-me-girl#the-goggles-do-nofin MEENAH: looks like you got the rainbow drinker thing going on too
      @kanaya_happy KANAYA: I Suppose
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: so
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you go around lookin like that all the time or
      @kanaya_idle:#Kind-Of-Personal? KANAYA: To My Knowledge Yes
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: heh
      @kanaya_talk KANAYA: Is There An Alternative Degree Of Auto Luminescence I Should Be Aware Of
      @kanaya_bored:#On-A-Scale-Of-One-To-Idiot KANAYA: And If So How Foolish Should I Feel For Only Learning About It Now
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: im no drinker buff but yeah our maryam figured out how to control it
      @kanaya_facepalm KANAYA: Really
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: she probably had more time to figure it out than you
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: when youre stuck in a busted session for three sweeps without much to do you figure some stuff out about yourself
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#buzzbugs#bzzzzz#hehe MEENAH: not my buzzbug wax but maybe you should axe her
      @kanaya_idle KANAYA: I Dont Think So
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: why not
      @kanaya_happy KANAYA: Id Like To
      @kanaya_smirktalk KANAYA: But I Cant Get Up The Nerve
      @meenah_happy:#you-check-out-her-ink-yet#fucken-dope MEENAH: aw come on shes cool
      @kanaya_idle KANAYA: Yes
      @kanaya_bored KANAYA: She Is An Amazing Person
      @kanaya_cry KANAYA: And It Is Very Intimidating
      @kanaya_facepalm KANAYA: I Had The Same Feelings Of Trepidation The Last Time I Encountered Someone I Admired
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: oh yeah who was that
      @kanaya_happy:#- KANAYA: ...
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: huh
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: you mean
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: her over there
      @meenah_happytalk:#her?? MEENAH: talky girl in the orange nighty jams
      @kanaya_smirklaugh:#-#- KANAYA: ...
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: i seaaa
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: saw you two hangin together last time
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: she your g frond
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: the red sort i mean
      @kanaya_smirklaugh:#-#-#- KANAYA: ...
      @kanaya_smirktalk:#-#-#-#-#Additional-Bashfully-Blank-Hash-Tags KANAYA: Maybe
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: thats adorbs yo
      <!--  -->
</args></action>
<action class='kanayaDialog2' name='Ask Kanaya to join.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_creepytalk MEENAH: hey maryam lookalike lets go kick the fuck outa skullzilla
      @kanaya_talk KANAYA: I Was About To Respond Favorably
      @kanaya_talk KANAYA: But Then I Glanced Over At Rose
      @kanaya_bored:#The-Limitless-Mysteries-Of-Her-Wisdom-Know-No-Bounds#Human-Sarcasm KANAYA: And She Was Just Shaking Her Head At Me Very Slowly And Kind Of Knowingly
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: no u silly drinker shes just fucking with you
      @kanaya_happytalk KANAYA: Oh Probably
      @kanaya_talk:#Bad-Plan KANAYA: But Lets Be Realistic Here The Answer Was Probably Going To Be No Anyway
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: aight well guess im going to drink skull guys blood all by my shellf then
      @kanaya_bored:#Gross-Monster-Blood KANAYA: I Bet It Tastes Really Bad
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: haha yeah
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: well later
      <!--  -->
</args></action>
<action class='daveDialog1' name='Talk to Dave.' command='talk'><args>
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: hey cape guy
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: youre uh
      @meenah_talk:#with-the-shades MEENAH: human whats his cape
      @dave_talk:#see-also#shaggy-2-cape DAVE: thats exactly my name
      @dave_smug DAVE: everyone stupidly insists on calling me dave though
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: so davecape
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: wheres your bro
      @dave_huh DAVE: my bro
      @dave_huhtalk:#like#the-ghostless-kind-of-dead-i-think DAVE: hes dead
      @dave_talk:#kid-bro#wtf DAVE: unless you mean the kid version as in the guy we both saw with the pointy shades
      @dave_madtalk:#thats-sorta-what-he-does#just-vanishes-like-a-mysterious-motherfucker DAVE: remember he grabbed my sleeping teen mom and flew away and that was the last i saw of him
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: no no
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: not that guy
      @meenah_happytalk:#one-of-the-best-hi-5s-eva#dudes-a-pro MEENAH: actually i gave him a sweet high five a little while ago but thats not who i mean
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: what when did you give him a high five
      @dave_madtalk:#not-cool DAVE: why wasnt i informed of this high five that took place
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: who cares im talking about your other bro
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#madvantas MEENAH: the cool shouty kid who got po'd and went to clamscray the f out
      @dave_idle DAVE: oh karkat you mean
      @dave_talk DAVE: i dunno hes around
      @dave_talk:#or-uh#being-talked-too DAVE: i saw him talking to his ancestor a while ago
      @dave_smug:#hilarious-toolparty DAVE: dont think he likes him very much
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: what
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: shouty shouldnt be hanging out with that glubbin dork
      @dave_smug:#ancestors#you-know-how-it-is DAVE: i doubt he actually wants to but you know how it is with ancestors
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: ...
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: ok maybe you dont since i guess youre actually an ancestor yourself
      @dave_talk:#i-think-her-name-was-fieri-or-something DAVE: or you were to some dead girl i never met but anyway
      @dave_idle DAVE: they just seem to
      @dave_huh DAVE: i dont know
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: have this inexplicable power over you
      @dave_concern:#shambles#kanaya#yeah DAVE: i mean look at kanaya over there shes a fucking shambles about hers
      @dave_concern:#dude-come-get-the-ruler DAVE: like it isnt even rational or anything they just represent something you measure yourself up to
      @dave_talk DAVE: and even though they probably arent all theyre cracked up to be it just kind of gets in your head you know
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: naw
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: my ancestor was fuckin lame
      @meenah_happytalk:#includin-a-pair-of-human-clown-slam-poets??#ahaha MEENAH: otoh in another tunaverse i grew up to be an ice cold murderbitch in charge of everybody which makes perfect sense
      @meenah_ohyes:#fuchsia-ruler MEENAH: so the only one i got to measure up to is me and it turns out i measure up awesomely
      @dave_talk DAVE: and on that day human whats his cape learned the only real treasure was a forced sense of self esteem
      @dave_idle DAVE: he thanked the punky sea princess for her radical wisdom and then she went away
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: i think
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: that
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: maybe i was just owned?
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='daveDialog2' name='Ask Dave to join.' command='talk'><args>
      @dave_idle DAVE: yeah i saw it
      @dave_talk:#daves-private-chill-time#eldritch-red-lobster#bargain-seafood-buffet#bored DAVE: i was looking up in space doing a little monster gazing right
      @dave_huhtalk:#ben-stiller-almost-fucking-tornadoed-in-his-grave DAVE: when suddenly i thought my glasses shattered
      @dave_huhtalk:#fuckin-relief#best-bro-gave-me-these DAVE: but it wasnt the shades turned out it was space itself that cracked
      @dave_concern:#monsters-dying#ghosts-dying#atrocious-problems DAVE: and i listened and i heard the screams and killing and stuff
      @dave_mad DAVE: havent slept well since that
      @dave_smug:#oh-yeah#i-forgot DAVE: well i guess im sleeping alright at the moment
      @dave_talk:#troll-anatomy#lewd#maybe? DAVE: cause im here in a bubble talking to you but yeah in general my shuteye has been boned up the protein chute
      @dave_talk:#awesome-projects DAVE: keeping myself busy with awesome projects helps a bit i guess
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: then you must want to kill the guy even worse than me
      @meenah_creepytalk:#what-good-is-a-cape-even#if-you-wont-fly-away-to-clobber-badguys MEENAH: why dont you join me we can fly away and fuck him up together 38)
      @dave_idle:#nah DAVE: nope
      @dave_talk:#dave_ebubbles DAVE: appreciate the offer but im just gonna hang tight and work on my ebubbles
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: e what
      @dave_smug:#how-is-this-not-awesome DAVE: ebubbles theyre awesome
      @dave_talk DAVE: its just some ridiculous shit i figured out how to do here
      @dave_talk:#just-as-long-as-you-dont-ask-me-how#we-are-cool DAVE: this whole place runs on memories so ive been messing around with that 
      @dave_smug DAVE: turns out i dont even really need the internet for shenanigans i can just exploit the afterlife
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: the fuuuck
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#stupid-waste-of-time MEENAH: i know youre down in the dumps kid but that sounds like a stupid waste of time
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: now come on lets go whale on a cherub
      @dave_idle:#yes-lets#just-fucking-with-you#no DAVE: nah
      @dave_huh DAVE: i mean
      @dave_huhtalk:#air-quotes DAVE: i think i might be "supposed" to kill him anyway?
      @dave_madtalk:#remember-that-bullshit-about-the-pimp-being-in-the-crib?#hahaha-oh-god DAVE: thats the feeling i get like there are all these clues about that ive kinda noticed
      @dave_madtalk:#i-heard-he-has-a-gold-tooth#are-you-fuckin-kidding-me DAVE: so if i am THE GUY that needs to take him down then fine ill do that if and when i get hornswoggled into some big showdown with a ridiculous green space pimp or whatever he is
      @dave_huhtalk:#im-better-at-comics DAVE: i dont know i think im not really cut out for the whole reluctant hero shtick
      @dave_huhtalk:#reluctant-before-it-was-cool#and-before-i-was-willing DAVE: like the whole scene is so obvious and trite and i cant even tell if my reluctance is ironic or if im playing it straight
      @dave_concern:#how-reluctant-do-you-even-have-to-BE-to-DOOOOO-something-like-etc-etc#sbahj DAVE: like ill wonder if im being reluctant enough to cut it or if im actually just being reluctant to be reluctant
      @dave_concern:#i-also-think-about-puppets-sometimes...#unrelated DAVE: it turns into like meta reluctance and then all i can think about is how fucking stupid the whole thing is
      @dave_talk:#ironic-self-pity DAVE: i think im probably just too self aware for this hero bullshit so dont even waste your time on me
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: wow
      @meenah_ohyes MEENAH: sooooo cooooooool
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: NOT
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='daveDialog3' name='Be Dave.' command='talk'><args>
      @dave_huh:#uh#w#t#f DAVE: wait
      @dave_huhtalk:#air-quotes DAVE: you want to "be me"?
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yeah why not
      @dave_madtalk:#a-face-presently-being-palmed DAVE: ok well without getting too deep into the issue of how absurd that request is on the very face of it
      @dave_mad DAVE: its just not going to happen
      @dave_talk DAVE: i mean not yet anyway not this early in your little dream bubble quest you got going on here
      @meenah_talk:#talk-at-peeps-in-your-koolkid-way#maybe-play-a-different-tune MEENAH: shut up dawg just lemme walk around as you and stuff
      @dave_idle DAVE: no
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: why
      @dave_talk DAVE: i really dont think we should get too meta about this
      @dave_huh:#ok DAVE: just
      @dave_concern DAVE: look
      @dave_concern:#cant-believe-im-even-explaining-this DAVE: youre on a mission to gather up all your dead friends and build an army or something
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: personally i think thats a shitty idea but you are clearly motivated to do that
      @meenah_idle:#tru-dat MEENAH: yea 
      @dave_huhtalk:#air-quotes DAVE: so why would you waste time going around "being other people" it doesnt make any fucking sense
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: for instance you cant be anybody in this fucking sandy beach area because ostenibly youre just charging through this place looking for your friends
      @dave_smug:#ahahaha#already-too-meta#i-give-the-fuck-up DAVE: dammit try to play the part at least somewhat
      @meenah_wut2:#boooring MEENAH: aw man
      @dave_talk DAVE: maybe when you catch up with your posse you can be some of those guys
      @dave_smug DAVE: hell maybe you can be some of us too after the whole thing youre trying to do winds up being this huge predictable disappointment
      @dave_talk DAVE: but that would have to be in a different area
      @meenah_fish:#what?#you-cray MEENAH: what area
      @dave_talk DAVE: like a different goddamn bubble zone
      @dave_talk DAVE: like someones memory of a magic fucking forest or home village or some shit
      @dave_talk DAVE: i dont know just somewhere the fuck else
      @dave_mad:#of-this#let-us-never-speak-again#be-dave?#bitch-please DAVE: now go away
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: FIN-E
      <!--  -->
</args></action>
</classes></sburb>
