<sburb>
	<classes>
		<action class='eavesdrop' command='talk' name='Yes.'><args>
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: N9w I realize we've 6een at this f9r s9me time already, 6ut at the risk 9f derailing the dial9gue y9u initiated, and may I just say h9w thrilled I am that y9u did, Karkat, I w9uld just like qualify my entire analysis 9f y9ur "Alternian culture" 6y saying that in c9ntrast with life 9n 6ef9rus, while y9ur pe9ple may have 6een engaged in vi9lent, lethal class struggle f9r milli9ns 9f sweeps, 6y n9 means d9es this imply that the 6ef9ran way 9f life was entirely with9ut pr96lematic elements, perhaps even m9re distur6ing and insidi9us f9r their lack 9f ackn9wledgement and 9pen discussi9n, particularly as a c9nsequence 9f what in my view were widely and dismayingly unexamined systemic s9cial injustices resulting fr9m the entrenched p9wer dynamics in play, dynamics strikingly similar t9 th9se 9f y9ur planet's markedly m9re 6ellic9se iterati9n, which has 9nly served t9 fully vindicate my hyp9thesis that such a hierarchy is really predicated 9n intrinsic dysfuncti9n, and failure t9 shift all the usual narratives and undiagn9sed pr96lems int9 an 9pen, judgment-free disc9urse thr9ugh which pr96lematic issues are c9nstructively channeled int9 m9re intelligently pr96lematized avenues 9f discussi9n.
      @kankri_talk2:#TW#9ppressi9n#culling#gru6-vi9lence#lusus-a6use#hem9ph96ia#pails#slurries#a6leism KANKRI: N9w 6ef9re I c9ntinue, it is 9nly decent 9f me t9 warn y9u a69ut certain triggers that are surely ahead in this essay. I mean c9nversati9n. Triggers include 6ut likely will n9t 6e limited t9 class 9ppressi9n, culling culture and vi9lence against gru6s, lusus a6use, c9mplementary and anal9g9us hate speech, pail filling, slurries and 9ther c9ncupiscent fluids, lifespan shaming, a6leist slurs, pr9lix dissertation... Actually, may6e it w9uld 6e easier f9r y9u t9 list y9ur triggers, and I'll d9 my 6est t9 av9id th9se t9pics, 9r navigate them m9re delicately, if at all p9ssi6le?
      @karkat_horror:# KARKAT: 
      @kankri_talk2:#c9ncillian9rmativity#micr9aggressi9ns#r9m-privilege#presumptu9us#m9irails#inexcusa6le KANKRI: Great. It s9unds like y9u d9n't have any triggers, at least n9ne that y9u kn9w a69ut. I'll pr9ceed with cauti9n nevertheless. Just please let me kn9w if y9u start feeling triggered 6y anything I'm saying, and we can take a 6rief time-9ut while y9u summ9n y9ur m9irail t9 help pacify y9u, assuming y9u have 9ne. N9t that I'm presuming y9u d9, 6ut I heard that y9u did, is that c9rrect? If n9t, I ap9l9gize. I further ap9l9gize if y9ur 9rientati9n precludes the p9ssi6ility, as a pale ar9mantic, panquadrant demir9mantic, s9mething in the gray palesexual department 9r such, and h9pefully y9u are n9t triggered 6y such presumptu9us c9ncillian9rmative language. It w9uldn't 6e the first time I was guilty 9f such an inexcusa6le micr9aggressi9n, and I am n9t s9 96livi9us t9 my 9wn r9mantic privilege t9 6elieve it will 6e the last time either.
      @karkat_horror:# KARKAT: 
      @kankri_talk4:#d9vetail#pr96lematic#p9wer-structures#t9xic-signist-language KANKRI: I'm glad I 6r9ught up the su6ject 9f unexamined privilege, 6ecause it d9vetails 6eautifully with the p9int I was a69ut t9 make regarding 6ef9ran s9ciety and its savage um6ral p9tentiality which later manifested thr9ugh the kind 9f Alternian 6rutality y9u are all t99 familiar with. Th9se in the higher echel9ns 9f the hem9spectrum such as the ceruleans, 9r "6lue 6l99ds" (careful, 6eing l99se with such termin9l9gy is 9pening the fl99dgates t9 a wh9le h9st 9f t9xic signist language and hem9ph96ic slurs), when addressing the challenges faced 6y th9se l9wer 9n the spectrum, such as the midhues 9r in particular warm castes like um6ers, 9chres, 9r "rust 6l99ds" (an9ther slur, highly pr96lematic, deeply 9ffensive and triggering termin9l9gy, str9ngly impl9ring y9u steer clear 9f this term), they w9uld 6e well advised t9 check their cerulean privilege, particularly 6ef9re dismissing hardships 9r marginalizing claims 9f 9ppressi9n, which can 6e difficult f9r them t9 identify 9r empathize with fr9m their advantage9us p9siti9n within the 6ef9ran//Alternian p9wer structures.
      @karkat_horror:# KARKAT: 
      @kankri_talk3:#p9st-spectral-w9rld#l9l#6U9Ys#9JAs#CIPs#R9yal-Vs#narratives#agendas#narratives#lifespan-privilege#dysfuncti9n#aweness#agendas KANKRI: And s9me may argue that in 9ur peaceful "ut9pian" culture that we have freed 9urselves fr9m injustice and disparities in privilege in a p9st-scarcity ec9n9my, largely equal rights distri6uted acr9ss the hem9spectrum, and theref9re exist in a "p9st-spectral w9rld" (laugh 9ut l9ud), and theref9re there is n9 need t9 champi9n imp9rtant s9cial causes and there is n9thing left t9 de6ate, 6ut really n9thing c9uld 6e further fr9m the truth. Y9u just need t9 educate y9urself and carefully investigate the l9ngstanding p9wer dynamics in play. F9r instance, a seemingly "harmless" remark fr9m a cis6l99ded cerulean t9ward an um6er 9r G9d f9r6id a 6urgundy 9r yes even a warm-identifying physically-c99ler caste, a69ut their very l9ng term future plans such as 9n the 9rder 9f centuries, then this may pr9ve t9 6e a very hurtful micr9agressi9n due t9 the fact that l9whues cann9t p9ssi6ly live that l9ng themselves, and the m9re priviliged caste c9uld easily 9utlive d9zens 9f generati9ns 9f midhues 9r hundreds 9f generati9ns 9f 6U9Ys (6urgundy-um6er-9chre-yell9wgreens, n9te please av9id descri6ing the latterm9st as "lime 6l99ds" as it has hist9rically 6een used as an especially vici9us epithet). Such remarks can further trigger painful reminders 9f h9w c99ler castes, t9 s9me extent 9JAs, 6ut CIPs and R9yal-Vs in particular, have 6een a6le t9 use their tremend9us lifespans 9ver the millenia t9 gain a strangleh9ld 9ver the s9cial 9rder, have 6een a6le t9 c9mpletely dictate 9ur s9cietal ev9luti9n 6y ensuring 9nly their cultural agendas and narratives receive the dial9gue's air supply, assuring the c9dificati9n 9f th9se resultant ideals and deciding what "n9rmalcy" entails, and sadly these a6s9lutes 6ec9me internalized acr9ss the full spectral range, even within th9se 9f m9st c9mpr9mised privilege, and s9 y9u 6egin t9 see the cyclical nature 9f the dysfuncti9n and the resulting inertia against p9sitive change and raising awareness 9f the m9st underpr96lematized issues, which I think we can agree, is pretty pr96lematic.
      @karkat_horror:# KARKAT: 
      @kankri_talk2:#underc9mplication#salty-fl9urish#rude-sh9uted-swear-w9rd#spectra6lind-s9ciety#dilemmas#g9als#Pr96lematics#dilemmas KANKRI: And really, it's every9ne's 6usiness t9 examine their privilege, even 6urgundies, wh9 may 6e su6ject t9 the pitfall 9f 6elieving inc9rrectly there are n9ne 9n the scale 6eneath them wh9m they enj9y certain privileges 9ver, which 9ff-spectrum tr9lls will never kn9w, such as th9se identifying as 9ther6l99ds 9r caste-multiples, "p9ly6l99ded", any wh9 hem9gl96ically ID as having a caste which manifests n9where (as yet kn9wn) in any9ne physically, 9r f9r that matter 9ffspecs wh9 physically d9 p9ssess such a 6l99d type, 9r "mutants" (VERY pr96lematic term, highly triggering t9 s9me, 6e warned), such as y9u and I, Karkat. 6ut this puts us 69th in a situati9n which t9 9ur kn9wledge uniquely all9ws us t9 understand and empathize with tragically underprivileged and unemp9wered gr9ups acr9ss all scuttles 9f life, thus aff9rding us 69th what I like t9 call a "uniquely underprivileged privilege", which, yes, is a kind 9f privilege we sh9uld 69th strive t9 check as well, whenever we can. This same uniquely underprivileged perspective as I'm sure y9u kn9w was disadvantaged up9n my p9st-scratch iterati9n as well, and while I have n9 d9u6t y9u justifia6ly came t9 revere that figure 9f y9ur planet's rich hist9ry and y9ur pers9nal lineage, and while his g9als 9f peace, equality, and a truly spectra6lind s9ciety, I'm afraid I pers9nally have tr9u6le c9nd9ning his meth9ds. I d9n't like t9 use the term "pr96lematic" lightly, 6ut, well, his tactics were n9thing if n9t massively pr96lematic, t9 say the least, empl9ying vi9lent uprising t9 effect change, and em6laz9ning his mark up9n hist9ry and his faithful f9ll9wers with the salty fl9urish 9f a single rude, sh9uted swear w9rd, it's n9t t9 my taste even th9ugh he is wh9 I w9uld have gr9wn up t9 6e in an9ther life. 6ut n9, I prefer t9 effect s9cial change thr9ugh rati9nal, h9nest disc9urse and c9ntri6uting t9 9ng9ing dial9gues, f9cusing 9n what sh9uld 6e the real g9als, thr9ugh keen adherence t9 the discipline 9f Pr96lematics, ensuring that we stay f9cused 9n successfully pr96lematizing a wide range 9f direly underc9mplicated s9cial dilemmas.
      @karkat_horror:# KARKAT: 
      @kankri_talk4:#TW#ancest9r-6ashing#shaming#swearing#t9rture#6urns#ship-sinking#struggles#invalidation#misgivings KANKRI: It's nice t9 see we agree 9n s9 much. May6e we are n9t s9 unalike, despite 9ur drastically different up6ringings. Anyway, as I was saying, the st9ry 9f y9ur ancest9r, and m9re imp9rtantly my exhaustive list 9f misgivings with his appr9ach t9 s9cial change, is quite a l9ng and ela69rate 9ne, 6ut it actually fits 6rilliantly within the larger m9saic which captures the 6r9ad str9kes 9f my p9st. I mean 9ur discussi9n. Trigger warnings f9r the f9ll9wing c9ntent include: ancest9r 6ashing, faith shaming, l9ud swearing, t9rture, 6urn w9unds, ship sinking... again, seri9usly, just let me kn9w if y9u 6egin t9 feel triggered 6y anything, even slightly. We'll pause and see if we can really expl9re th9se issues, and identify exactly h9w I may have invalidated y9ur struggles. With9ut further ad9, the st9ry is as f9ll9ws:
      @kankri_talk2~dialogimg_kankri1  
      @kankri_talk3~dialogimg_kankri1  
      @kankri_glance~dialogimg_kankri1  
      @kankri_talk4~dialogimg_kankri2 
      @kankri_talk2~dialogimg_kankri2 
      @kankri_talk3~dialogimg_kankri2 
      @karkat_horror:#...................... KARKAT: 
      @karkat_horror KARKAT: 
      <!--  -->
		</args></action>
		<action class='latulaTalk1' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Talk to Latula.'><args>
      @latula_happier LATULA: d4mn grrrrl!!!!
      @latula_happytalk:#>8D LATULA: you f1n4lly m4d3 1t! h1gh f1v3!!!
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: you know it
      @meenah_happytalk:#oOoOoO MEENAH: i am so fuckin ghostly now
      @latula_happy LATULA: r1ght on grl!!!! dr34m bubz rul3!
      @latula_shades1 LATULA: 4-l1f3 4LYF3!!!
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: wha
      @latula_shine:#spok3n-qu1rk-confus1on LATULA: 4h4h4 y34h. th4t should h4v3 sound3d l1k3 "4 l1f3 for lyf3" l1k3 'A' 4s 1n 4ft3r, but spok3n 4s 4 numb3r, th3n '4' 4s 4 homonym for th3 pr3pos1t1on 4nd stuff!!!!
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: you know how 1t 1s. 4 grlz gott4 s4cr1f1c3 und3rst4nd4b1l1ty for th3 s4k3 of r4dn3ss som3t1m3z.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: preach1n to the group of coral s1ngers pyrope
      @latula_talk LATULA: cor4l s1ng3rs? oh you m34n cho1r, 1 g3t 1t!!! but cor4l 4s 1n th3 funky sh1t und3rw4t3r 1nst34d, h4h4h?
      @latula_happytalk:#punz#k1nd-of-l4m3 LATULA: st1ll rock1ng th3 f1sh punz 1 s33. w3ll th4ts not r34lly th3 k1nd of r4dn3ss 1 w4s t4lk1ng 4bout, but 1ll l3t 1t sl1d3.
      @meenah_angry MEENAH: hey fuck you!
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: cant B-ELI-EV-E yall go shitting on my fish puns right outta the blowhole like that
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#or-should-i-say#(s)word(fish)play?#nah-that-sux MEENAH: as if your numbers bs and jacking zees on the end a words is any more rad than my baller wordplay
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: i mean your skating and stunts are objectively rad ill give you that 
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: but you need to get off your high seahorse because practically NOFIN else about you is especially radder than average
      @latula_happier LATULA: oh ch1ll AX3, p4ych3ck!!! 1 4m so j3rk1ng your fork!
      @latula_happytalk:#tow1ng-lo4ds-h4rsh3s-my-gr1nds LATULA: 1 know w3v3 h4d our 1ssu3z b3for3. but 1 could 4lw4ys s33 you h4d tru r4dgrl cr3d. you dont 3v3n know how h4rd 1t w4s tow1ng th3 R4D LO4D 4ll by mys3lf w1th you gon3 for so long!!!!
      @latula_angry LATULA: do you 3v3n know how l4m3 of 4 sc3n3 1t 1s b31ng th3 only l3g1t 1n your f4c3 pow3rg4m1ng grl 1n 4 bunch of bubbl3s full of brut4l pos3rz???
      @latula_happier:#H1-F1V3 LATULA: wh4t 1m s4y1ng 1s, 1m psych3d to h4v3 you b4ck mp. h3y h1t m3 up top!
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: uh sure
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: still wearing out the highfives i sea even after like what
      @meenah_annoyed:#still-dont-know-how-time-works-here MEENAH: eternity?
      @latula_happy LATULA: fuck y34h grl.
      @latula_angry LATULA: OH!!!!
      @latula_laugh:#k1ll3d-th3-SH1T-out-of-us LATULA: n3v3r 3v3n got to congr4tul4t3 you on how W1CK3D your r4d su1c1d3 bomb pl4n w4s! >8D
      @latula_tongue LATULA: n3v3r s4w 1t com1ng!!!! sur3 n3v3r sm3ll3d 1t com1ng, h3h. 
      @latula_happytalk:#not-th4t-th4t-r34lly-3v3n-n33d3d-3xpl41n1ng? LATULA: w4y sm4rt. t1m1ng 1t just b3for3 th3 scr4tch, so th4t god t13rz d1dnt h4v3 4 ch4nc3 to r3v1v3 b3for3 th3 r3s3t, thus 1ron1c4lly l34v1ng th3m to b3 3r4s3d from 3x1st3nc3.
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: th4t JUST occurr3d to m3 r3c3ntly. wuz op3n1ng th3 m34l v4ult to m4k3 4 fr34k1n ghost sn4ck wh3n 1 wuz l1k3. SH1T!!!! 
      @latula_angry LATULA: P444444YCH3CK!!! 1 s41d, 4ll sh4k1ng my f1st.
      @latula_happier:#H1-F1V3 LATULA: h4h4h4, dont l34v3 m3 h4ng1n grl. >8D
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: k one more pyrope but thats it
      @meenah_wut:#hi5-fatigue MEENAH: i dig a good highfive as much as the next badgirl but my cod
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: got this fresh pimp ghost bod looking fine as fuck i dont need to callous up my palms already
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: havent you heard an empress needs hands so soft you can use em to polish gold with???
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='latulaTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Ask Latula to join.'><args>
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: question
      @latula_idle LATULA: shoot b4b3z.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: seeing as what a hot shit gamer gurl you have a reputation for and all
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: i figured you would be a lock to join my party
      @meenah_creepy:#lord-of-clams MEENAH: to go fuck up clamilord or whoever
      @latula_huh LATULA: w41t. who???
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: skull guy
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: kills ghosts
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: 3rrr nop3. h3lp m3 out p4ymon3y.
      @meenah_wut2:#current-like-water-current-yessss MEENAH: dont you keep up with current events
      @latula_talk LATULA: tchhh, your3 r3m1nd1ng m3 why 1 thought you w3r3 cr4zy mp. just fr34k1n sp1ll 1t.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: the shit in the sky
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: it cracked 
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: a monster did that
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: DO YOU WANT TO GO )(-ELP M-E KILL T)(-E BAD GUY???????
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: oh why d1dnt you s4y so!!!
      @latula_talk LATULA: sounds l1k3 4 r4d pl4n 4nd you know how 1 f33l 4bout th3 r4dpl4nz....
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: but??
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: h4t3 to b3 4 buzzk1ll but... 1ts b33n wh4t.
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: 4pprox1m4t3ly H3LLA y34rz s1nc3 1 d1d 4ny f1ght1ng????
      @latula_talk:#tw#h3mophob1c-slurs LATULA: k1nd of rusty. sh1t dont l3t kk know 1 s41d rusty, 4h4h4.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: so
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: so 1m s4y1ng 1 h4d SCADZ of t1m3 to p3rf3ct th1s K1LL3R HAND PLANT!!! >8D
      @latula_stunt LATULA: w4nn4 s3333?
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: no pretty sure dont give much a shit about a trick you do on your four wheel device
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: tho i will say
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: "scads" is actually a fish pun you made probly on accident
      @meenah_fishtalk:#fish-puns-are#my-one-weakness-:( MEENAH: which kind of makes me want to give you a hug so it balances out your dumb shit answer
      @latula_annoyedtalk:#tho-m4yb3-you-l1k3-w3t-snuggl3pl4n3s?#s1nc3-you-c4n-l1v3-und3r-w4t3r? LATULA: 1m sorry mp. 1 r34lly 4m!!! f33l l1k3 such 4 w3t snuggl3pl4n3 b41l1ng on you l1k3 th1s.
      @latula_idle3 LATULA: 1 should prob4bly run 1t by mt. s33 wh4t h3 th1nks.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: oh shit you and captor
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: thats still a thing after all this pseudotime or
      @latula_idle LATULA: h4h4 y3444h.
      @meenah_idle:#38o MEENAH: still red??????
      @latula_idle LATULA: uh huh. >8]
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: mother glubber
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: seriously didnt think T)(ATD last
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: 1dk, th3r3z w4y mor3 to h1m th4n. w3ll, 4ll th3 t3rr1bl3 4nd stup1d sh1t h3 s4ys 4ll th3 t1m3.
      @latula_talk LATULA: 4nd 1ts 4lw4yz f3lt l1k3 h3 n33ds m3 1f th4t m4k3s s3ns3, 3v3n 4ft3r dy1ng. so th3r3z th4t!!!!
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: fuckin afterlife
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: i know im new here but
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: almost seems like
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: you die and nothing means anyfin and then you date forever
      @meenah_happytalk:maybe-in-a-nice-way-tho?? MEENAH: sort of makes me want to puke
      @latula_happier LATULA: >;D
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#anemone-waaay... MEENAH: couldnt see that wink behind your radspex fyi
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: if you change your mind
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: just lemminnow
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='latulaTalk3' command='talk' sprite='meenah' name='Be Latula.'><args>
      @latula_bored LATULA: grl, who DO3SNT w4nt to b3 m3???
      @latula_angry LATULA: you th1nk you c4n just w4ltz 1nto th1s bubbl3 4nd st4rt b31ng 4ny r4d g4m3r grl you cross p4thz w1th????
      @latula_happytalk:#cr4dz#tm LATULA: chy34h, R1GHT! you h4v3 4 long, LONG w4y to go b3for3 you 34rn 3nough r4d-cr3dz to b3 M3. or 4s 1 l1k3 to c4ll th3m, CRADZ.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: latula shut up and just tell me what horseshit thing you want me to do
      @latula_idle LATULA: 1ts gonn4 cost y4!
      @latula_talk:#th3-numb3r-413#not-'AIE' LATULA: you h4v3 to 'l1k3' 4ll my r4dd3st m3mor13z, 4nd th3n r3bubbl3 4t l34st 413 of th3m.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: you can NOT be serious
      @latula_laugh:#psych3 LATULA: H4H4H4H4H4H4!
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: kay tules im outtie
      @latula_annoyed:#hmzzz... LATULA: w41t! dont b3 l1k3 th4t, w3 c4n st1ll cut 4 d34l, l3mm3 th1nk.
      @latula_talk LATULA: 4lr1ght, k1d. t3ll you wh4t. s1nc3 1 d1g your styl3, 1ll g1v3 you 4 shot.
      @latula_talk LATULA: you m4y th1nk you rul3, wh3r34z most oth3rs drool, but wh4t 1 w4nt to know 1s, how b4d c4n you THR4SH stuff?
      @latula_talk LATULA: just n33d to scop3 your k1ckfl1p chopz, m4k3 sur3 3v3ryth1ng ch3cks out. s33 1f your t3chn1qu3s 4r3 wh3r3 th3y n33dz to b3 4t.
      @meenah_wut2:#sdlkjlkjfs MEENAH: kickflip chops
      @latula_laugh LATULA: y34h grl. show m3 y3r stuntz. m4yb3 som3th1ng 1n 4 h4ndpl4nt. ooh, know wh4t sh1t would b3 W1CK3D M4L1C1OUS?
      @latula_angry:#Y3AH!!!#hold-pol3s LATULA: gr1nd1ng down 4 R41L1NG!!!!
      @latula_happytalk:#'4'-1s-4-homonym-4g41n-yo LATULA: th4t ought to b3 fl4gr4nt 3nough to prov3 your r4dn3ss 4 SHOR3.
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: so wh4t4y4 s4y, p4ych3ck? you r34dy to st4rt r1pp1ng up so m4ny h3ll4c3ous shr3ds th4t th1s f13rc3sh1tty b1zn4sty w1ll st4rt g3tt1ng so d3l1r1ously rud3br4z3n 1t... 
      @meenah_angry MEENAH: just gimme the board pyrope
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='porrimTalk1' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Talk to Porrim.'><args>
      @porrim_happy PORRIM: Welco+me back.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: sup maryam
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: So+, yo+ur death certificate has barely dried, and yo+u're already busy raising an army, I hear?
      @meenah_talk:#dag MEENAH: howd you even hear that already
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Wo+rd travels fast here. Plenty o+f go+ssip.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk:#Bubblr PORRIM: No+ o+ne quite prepares yo+u fo+r the fact that o+n the o+ther side o+f death is an infinite echo+ chamber o+f teen drama.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Funny ho+w when we left o+ur wo+rld to+ play yo+ur game, we all tho+ught we were leaving o+ur juvenile scho+o+lfeeding days behind us. 
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yeah
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: all the more reason to get out of here and fight bad guys and stuff
      @porrim_happytalk:#Nicely-do+ne. PORRIM: I no+ticed ho+w yo+u cunningly sidestepped an enco+unter with Kankri do+wn there.
      @meenah_wut2:#poor-shouty-38( MEENAH: yeaaah
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: nomoby deserves havin to meet a dead teen alt universe ancestor like that
      @porrim_laugh PORRIM: I think he might be entertaining so+me delusio+n o+f taking him under his wing.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Or if no+t his wing, the red fuzzy arm o+f his sweater.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: what is with that ugly thing anyway
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I made it fo+r him, actually.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk:Pantskan PORRIM: Fo+r o+ne thing, I go+t tired o+f lo+o+king at his stupid hiked up pants, which he refused to+ change, ever. Serio+usly, did yo+u ever see him wearing anything else?
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: haha no
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: So+ unfashio+nable.
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: Also+, he was always shivering. It gets kind o+f chilly o+ut here, and he just wo+uldn't sto+p. No+t that I minded to+o+ much, but he just has this way o+f making such vo+cal and o+stentatio+us displays o+f suffering, like it's so+me kind o+f righteo+us state o+f being. It gets difficult fo+r everyo+ne to+ endure, especially after eo+ns. Hence his nickname, I guess.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: wait nickname
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: if theres some new dig on vantas i need to know about it pronto
      @porrim_happy PORRIM: The Insufferable.
      @meenah_creepylaugh MEENAH: fuck yes highfive
      @meenah_wut:#goddamn-radgirl MEENAH: wait forget it my hands still sore from latula
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: bitch slaps )(ARD
      @porrim_happier PORRIM: Oh, I kno+w.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: you do
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: wait that is soundin fishily like innuendo
      @meenah_wink:#uh... MEENAH: you and her ever uh
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I was under the impressio+n yo+u didn't co+me here to+ start trading go+ssip.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: whoa youre right
      @meenah_talk:#glub-exactly-zero-fucks MEENAH: almost forgot to not be glubbin a fuck
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: i apologize for prying into your romlife that was so shrimpudent of me
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: It's alright. It's no+t like I have many well kept secrets. 
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Co+me visit any time. We'll get yo+u all caught up o+n exactly who+'s been seen passing thro+ugh the well-greased revo+lving do+o+rs to+ my quadrants.
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='porrimTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Ask Porrim to join.'><args>
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: It's a no+ble idea.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: But I do+n't kno+w ho+w useful I'd be.
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: oh come praaaaawn 38[
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: What's the size o+f yo+ur party so+ far?
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: uh
      @porrim_happy PORRIM: It's still just yo+u, isn't it?
      @meenah_fish:#losers#everywhere MEENAH: ... maybe
      @porrim_talk:#Go+d-tiers PORRIM: If I were yo+u, I'd ask all the go+d tiers first. They'd give yo+u the mo+st tactical advantage, wo+uldn't they?
      @porrim_talk:#Pajama-party PORRIM: Then yo+u can build yo+ur co+alitio+n aro+und them.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: i guess
      @porrim_idle PORRIM: +, they're immo+rtal, right? Or... gho+st immo+rtal, perhaps?
      @porrim_idle:#Gho+st-immo+rtality#Serio+us-business PORRIM: Dear Go+d, it's finally co+me to+ this. We have to+ talk abo+ut "gho+st immo+rtality" no+w, in a serio+us way?
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: lol yeah
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Anyway, that's what I'd do+.
      @meenah_talk:#at-least...#ghost-god-tiers MEENAH: but i think the thing is the skull lord might actually be able to kill god tiers?
      @porrim_surprise PORRIM: Can he?
      @meenah_talk:#whaaaaales#&lt;3 MEENAH: like bypass the whole judgment hullabeluga that makes em resurrect
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you know with the fancy clock and all
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: i dunno
      @porrim_annoyedtalk:#Sylph-o+f-Wo+rds PORRIM: Yo+u'll have to+ ask Aranea. I'm sure she co+uld talk yo+ur fin o+ff o+n the subject.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: oof
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: yeah maybe later
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Do+ yo+u even kno+w who+ all the go+d tiers are?
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: um
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: There's Aranea. Did yo+u ask her?
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: yeah but she has her own plan
      @meenah_talk:#eff-that MEENAH: girl is going on a cherub jam or some bitch ass noise
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Ok. Well, I ho+pe this isn't to+o+ invasive, but what abo+ut yo+u?
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: ...
      @porrim_happytalk:#Except-presumably-Damara... PORRIM: I've heard rumo+rs that yo+u reached go+d tier, but never let o+n to+ anyo+ne.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: you dont understand
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#looked-like-such-ass MEENAH: its just that fucking thief of life getup
      @meenah_wut:#got-a-reputation-to-conchsider MEENAH: i couldnt just parade around in that hideous thing
      @porrim_happy PORRIM: So+ it is true, then. Tho+ught so+.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: See what I mean, tho+ugh? I wasn't sure abo+ut that until just no+w. Rumo+rs are always flying, but secrets so+meho+w persist.
      @porrim_laugh PORRIM: Who+ kno+ws who+ else reached go+d tier? A lo+t can happen in three sweeps. I o+nly kno+w I didn't make it.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: But if yo+u need so+meo+ne to+ eerily pho+spho+resce in the demo+n's vicinity, while debating whether to+ try drinking his blo+o+d, then I'd like to+ think I easily crack the to+p 10+ candidates yo+u might co+nsider fo+r the jo+b.
      @meenah_happy:#po-glow MEENAH: yeah i know youd rock the glowin duties
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: guess youre right i should sea what other god tiers want to join
      @meenah_talk:#lame#terrible MEENAH: the prob is that i dont think becoming god tier stops you from being lame and terrible
      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#soooo MEENAH: and we got a lot of people like that on our team
      @porrim_idle PORRIM: This is true.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: guess ill keep axin around
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: gonna bounce seaya meryam
      <!--  -->
</args></action>



<action class='porrimTalk3' sprite='latula' command='talk' name='Talk to Porrim.'><args>
      @latula_talk:#GRLZ-1N-D4-H1V3 LATULA: yo porz, you s33 p4yd1rt 1s b4ck??? 
      @porrim_idle PORRIM: I saw.
      @latula_talk:#l3ss-drool#mor3-rul3 LATULA: pr3tty r4d huh?? th3 4-lyf3 just scor3d 4 l1ttl3 mor3 GRL POW3R!!!!
      @latula_idle LATULA: h3y g1mm3 f1v3!
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: That's... OW.
      @porrim_angry PORRIM: No+t so+ hard!
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: That's go+o+d.
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: wh444t, com3 on. 1 thought you of 4ll p3opl3 would b3 psych3d to g3t 4 l1l mor3 r3pr3z3nt4t1on from th3 l4d13s UP 1NZ.
      @porrim_idle:#Up-inz#Meaningless#On-all-levels PORRIM: Why would that be? It's nice to see an old friend, but that's about it.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I think you are possibly still caricaturizing my point of view on the subject, assuming we're even talking about the same subject.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Much the way yo+ur co+ntinued co+mmitment to+ this o+verzealo+us "rad girl" thing still strikes me as a caricature o+f the kind o+f female strength and empo+werment yo+u're trying to+ pro+ject.
      @latula_angry LATULA: s4y wh4t??? th4tz bogus, 1m th1s r4d b3c4us3 1 l1k3 b31ng r4d! r4dn3ss rul3z.
      @porrim_talk:#Did-I-pho+netically-emphasize-that-'z'-eno+ugh? PORRIM: I kno+w it rulez. But there's such a thing as o+verdo+ing it.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Do+n't yo+u think it can co+me acro+ss as a series o+f affectatio+ns designed to+ o+verco+mpensate fo+r an implicit flaw with yo+ur gender? An act which rebuts what sho+uld be a straw man, with a carto+o+nish masquerade that with every kickflip and high five screams "YES, IT APPEARS THAT GIRLS CAN BE AS RADICAL AND AS GOOD AT GAMES AS BOYS!" thus lending a certain dignity to+ the premise at the expense o+f yo+ur o+wn?
      @latula_huh:#r4dt1m3z-off1c14lly:#H4RSH3D LATULA: wh4... w41t wh4t? 4w m4n.
      @latula_shades2:#h4lp LATULA: wh4t you t4lk1ng 4bout grl. m33n4h wh3r3d you go! com3 h3lp m3 b3 cyn1c4l 4bout th1s! 4h!!!
      @porrim_annoyed2:#Fuschia-do+wn-matriarchy#Purple-do+wn-patriarchy PORRIM: Yo+u can pretend to+ misunderstand all yo+u want, but we've talked abo+ut this befo+re and I kno+w yo+u're smarter abo+ut this than yo+u let o+n. We were raised in what was a fo+rmally "matriarchal so+ciety", which has always been used as a shield to+ do+wnplay clear instances o+f female o+ppressio+n and o+bfuscate the relevance o+f gender ro+les, particularly where they're weighted against females. But anyo+ne who+'s lo+o+ked at o+ur so+ciety mo+re ho+nestly can see that while, yes, it is superficially o+bserved as a matriarchy o+n a fuschia-do+wn basis, o+n a practical level all o+f the enfo+rcement and po+litical po+wer go+verning mo+st classes was delegated to+ the higher CIPs, which were generally male-do+minated castes. They go+t to+ co+ntro+l the agenda and dictate the so+cial co+nventio+ns, and anyo+ne who+ dared to+ o+bject o+r bring light to+ this co+uld always be co+untered with "Hey! Matriarchy! End o+f discussio+n."
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: grl, pl34s3. dont t3ll m3 your3 go1ng full v4nt4s on m3 h3r3. 
      @porrim_angrytalk PORRIM: No+, if I were getting my Vantas o+n, we'd o+nly be getting warmed up. But that's really all I have to+ say o+n the matter.
      @latula_tongue LATULA: wh3w!
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: I just think yo+u sho+uld be yo+urself mo+re o+ften. We already kno+w yo+u are stro+ng and go+o+d at games and all that. Yo+u have no+thing to+ pro+ve.
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: y34h. your3 prob4bly r1ght.
      @latula_talk:#sp3c14lly-wh3n-1m-off-my-m3ds LATULA: 1ts k1nd of str3ssful som3t1m3s, k33p1ng 1t up! som3t1m3s 1 forg3t to put z33s on th3 3nd of words, 4nd 1 r34lly str3ss out 4bout 1t.
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: you know, 1 4lw4ys d1d f33l b3tt3r t4lk1ng to you. l1k3 1 could t4k3 th3 3dg3 off my r4d th1ng, 4nd r3l4x 4 l1ttl3 mor3.
      @porrim_happier:#:) PORRIM: Then let's make it mo+re o+f a habit, shall we?
      @latula_happier LATULA: h3ckz y3s!!!
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: h3y, th4nks for th3 p3pt4lk, popo m3rryg4mz.
      @porrim_annoyed PORRIM: That nickname.
      @porrim_annoyed PORRIM: It
      @porrim_surprise PORRIM: It is just so+ awful.
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: oh whoopz.
      @latula_talk LATULA: w4nt m3 to sw1tch b4ck to pornst4r???
      @porrim_idle PORRIM: ...
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: Merrygamz will be fine.
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='kankriTalk1' sprite='latula' command='talk' name='Talk to Kankri.'><args>
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: bro!!!! 1 h34r youv3 b33n h4ssl1ng th3 n3w k1dz. wh4t 1s UP w1th th4t???
      @kankri_talk:#New-f9ll9wers KANKRI: Hassling? Far fr9m it. I've merely disc9vered a new and far less ungrateful fl9ck which has n9t yet 6ec9me w9efully jaded t9 my messages 9f p9sitive s9cial change.
      @latula_talk LATULA: you c4nt fool m3 k4nkz. you 4r3 bor1ng th4t poor dud3 to d34th. you just w4nt to m4k3 4 ghost out of h1m so you c4n k33p h1m h3r3 for3v3r.
      @karkat_horror KARKAT: 
      @latula_talk:#r3:#m1st4k3s#l1k3-us LATULA: wh1ch 41nt r1ght! you h4v3 to l3t th4t bro d13 of h1s own M4D VOL1T1ONZ. 
      @kankri_talk4:#I-mean,-c9nversati9n. KANKRI: Can y9u sc99t away 9n y9ur little wheeled t9y f9r immature wigglers? I was in the middle 9f a serm9n.
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: why dont you s4v3 h1m som3 gr13f 4nd g1v3 h1m on3 of your old m3moz?
      @latula_talk:#fru1ty-r1ght3ous-blowh4rd-f4ctory LATULA: 4h4h4h, r3m3mb3r thoz3??? how m4ny sw33ps d1d you sp3nd try1ng to forc3 us to r34d th4t tr4sh?
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: I d9n't remem6er. And n9, I w9n't 6e sharing my 9ld mem9s with him. They were written very p99rly, and my meth9ds 9f argumentati9n were flawed and extremely childish. I've deleted m9st 9f th9se mem9ries fr9m these 6u66les, s9 d9n't 69ther r99ting ar9und f9r them. Frankly, they stunk.
      @latula_annoyed:#>8[ LATULA: h3y!
      @kankri_talk:#tw#tw#tw#s9rry#tw#a6leism KANKRI: 9h, man, I'm s9rry. I c9mpletely f9rg9t that "stunk" was an a6leist slur. Please f9rgive my insensitivity t9ward y9ur disa6ility.
      @latula_shine LATULA: 1tz ch1ll, 1 w4s only 4ct1ng off3nd3d to bug you.
      @kankri_talk:#Trigger-warning:#Em6arrassed-retracti9ns-ahead KANKRI: N9, really, it was inexcusa6le 9f me. I sh9uld have at least preceded my call9us remark with a trigger warning.
      @kankri_talk3:#Nasal-privilege#H9riz9ns#6r9adness#H9riz9ntal-width-l9ngenning KANKRI: I have n9 6usiness making light 9f y9ur impairment, thus failing t9 check my nasal privilege, and p9tentially 6ringing 6ack painful and devastatingly triggering mem9ries 9f the 9ld cycle 9f revenge 6etween y9u and s9me friends which resulted in the l9ss 9f y9ur 9lfact9ry sense. I have t9 admit, I was skeptical at first a69ut whether that really qualified as a true disa6ility warranting sensitivity and the pr9m9ti9n 9f awareness, 6ut 6eing cl9se t9 y9u as a friend and carefully examining my privilege has really 9pened my eyes. 99ps, that euphemism is slightly a6leist t9 the 6lind, what I meant was "6r9adened my h9riz9ns 9n the nature 9f disa6ility." S9rry.
      @latula_happytalk:#MAD-d1s4dv4nt4g3d-brot1m3z LATULA: y34h! th4ts funny, c4us3 1t n3v3r would h4v3 occurr3d to m3 to t4k3 1t 4ll th4t s3r1ously 4s 4 h4nd1c4p w1thout you m4k1ng 4 f3d3r4l c4s3 out of 1t for so long on my b3h4lf. so, th4nkz k4nk!!!
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: My pleasure. Really, it is truly amazing that y9u have managed t9 triumph 9ver such adversity t9 6ec9me a great r9le m9del f9r 9thers, excellent at vide9 games, and a t9tally stellar skate69arding pers9n, all while 6eing a girl, n9 less.
      @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: 
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='kankriTalk2' sprite='latula' command='talk' name='Be Kankri.'><args>
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: 6e me? I...
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: I'm n9t sure if that's...
      @latula_happier LATULA: 4w com3 on k4nkl3z!!! pl33333334z3???
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Well...
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: 9k. I'll interrupt my imperative m9n9l...dial9gue just this 9nce.
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: F9r y9u.
      <!--  -->
</args></action>



<action class='latulaTalk4' sprite='porrim' command='talk' name='Talk to Latula.'><args>
      @porrim_happy PORRIM: Hey.
      @latula_shine LATULA: yo yo, w4zzup grl!!!
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Latula, it's just me. I do+n't think anyo+ne is lo+o+king. No+ need to+ go+ so+ heavy o+n the rad girl ro+utine.
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: y34h, gu3ss your3 r1ght. 1'll ch1ll 1t down 4 b1t.
      @latula_talk LATULA: wh4ts on your th1nk p4n, po-m4ry.
      @porrim_talk:#Descesto+rs?#Ancendants?#Dancesto+rs...#Hmm#Bingo+ PORRIM: Meeting o+ur ancesto+rs as kids, o+r, I mean o+ur descendants as kids, ho+wever yo+u want to+ spin it...
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: It has me thinking abo+ut o+ur rebo+o+ted lives o+n Alternia, and what we grew up to+ be. 
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Makes me wo+nder abo+ut fate. If it's so+mething that's even co+mprehensible.
      @latula_idle LATULA: y34h?
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: Fo+r instance, o+n Alternia, my relatio+nship with Kankri seemed to+ make so+me sense. I co+uld definitely see o+ur lives beco+ming entangled in that way, karmically speaking.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: But then there were o+ther develo+pments that are still mysterio+us to+ me.
      @porrim_talk:#Radglare#Kindfang PORRIM: Like, as far as I kno+w, yo+u and Aranea always go+t alo+ng. Didn't yo+u?
      @latula_annoyedtalk LATULA: 3h 1 gu3ss. n3v3r sp3nt much t1m3 th1nk1ng 4bout s3rk3t, tbh.
      @latula_bored:#zzzz#not-3v3n-th3-r4d-k1nd-of-z33s LATULA: 4lw4ys thought sh3 w4s 4 s3lf 4bsorb3d snooz3, 1f you r34lly w4nt to know.
      @porrim_talk:#Redglare#Mindfang PORRIM: Exactly. No+thing much to+ yo+ur relatio+nship to+ speak o+f at all. But in yo+ur po+st-scratch lives yo+u had such majo+r issues to+gether, even yo+ur descendants inherited it, and co+ntinued the co+ntentio+us cycle until there was blo+o+dshed.
      @latula_huh LATULA: r34lly?
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: huh. 
      @porrim_annoyed:#Mindfang-gave-yo+u-five#Then-left-yo+u-hanging PORRIM: Did yo+u no+t kno+w that?
      @latula_talk LATULA: n3v3r r34lly thought 4bout 1t. but now th4t you m3nt1on 1t, th4t outcom3 m4k3s 4ll sorts of s3ns3 to m3.
      @porrim_annoyed PORRIM: It do+es? Ho+w?
      @latula_idle LATULA: just do3s, b4b3z.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I do+n't really understand karma.
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: th4ts c4us3 your3 not 4 m1nd pl4y3r.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Oh. Co+uld yo+u explain to+ me ho+w it wo+rks, then?
      @latula_shades2:#do-1-look-l1k3-s3rk3t-to-you??? LATULA: pshh, 4s 1f. th4t wouldnt b3 4 v3ry r4d th1ng to do.
      @latula_happier LATULA: h3y, ch3ck out th1s OUTST4ND1NG h34lfl1p!!!!
      @porrim_surprise PORRIM: I do+n't
      @porrim_annoyed:#Sigh PORRIM: ...
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: Ok. Let's see it.
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='kankriTalk3' sprite='porrim' command='talk' name='Talk to Kankri.'><args>
      @porrim_angrytalk PORRIM: Kanny, leave this po+o+r kid alo+ne.
      @kankri_talk2:#micr9aggressi9ns#n9-wait#MACR9agressi9ns-m9re-like KANKRI: I'd appreciate it if y9u w9uldn't call me that. We've talked a69ut this. That's what y9u call a wiggler. D9 I l99k like a wiggler t9 y9u, P9rrim? N9, I d9n't. It's 6een three sweeps, plus eternity, f9r, excuse me, "fuck's" sake. I think we can safely retire that particular term 9f "endearment". Call me anything 6ut that, even my 9ther nickname. I'm actually 9k with that 9ne.
      @porrim_talk:#And-even-then,-pro+bably-no+t-to+-yo+ur-face. PORRIM: I'm no+t calling yo+u Insufferable, Kanny. Well, no+t unless I'm using it as an actual adjective. 
      @porrim_annoyed:#No+t-o+ften-I-mean. PORRIM: Well... 
      @kankri_talk3:#Fresh#Faced#Y9ungster#Kn9wledge-thirst KANKRI: It w9uld 6e nice if y9u'd at least use my pr9per name in fr9nt 9f my studi9us y9ung Alternian descendant. It really kind 9f er9des my credi6ility, and I d9n't need that in the pr9ximity 9f a fresh faced y9ungster wh9 clearly thirsts f9r kn9wledge. Why w9uld y9u want t9 sa69tage a fine y9ung man's educati9n like that?
      @porrim_idle PORRIM: Ro+lling my eyes here.
      @porrim_light PORRIM: Can yo+u see? Do+ yo+u want me to+ light them up fo+r yo+u?
      @kankri_glance:#H9w-d9-y9u-even-r9ll-eyes-with9ut-pupils? KANKRI: N9, 6ut thanks f9r 9ffering. C9uld y9u g9 r9ll them 9ver there? Thank y9u. N9w where was I.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: I do+n't think he cares.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Hey, there. Karkat? If yo+u do+n't mind my asking... are yo+u even remo+tely interested in the lo+af supplement this guy's serving?
      @karkat_sullen KARKAT: 
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Go+tcha. Yo+u just said all yo+u needed to+ say.
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: Yo+u kno+w, yo+u are actually very cute. 
      @porrim_happytalk PORRIM: That girl who+'s been wandering aro+und in the drago+n suit is a very lucky lady. 
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: 9k, w9nderful. That c9nversati9n just came t9 an end. 
      @kankri_talk2:#It's-weird KANKRI: P9rrim, please d9n't hit 9n my re699ted kid ancest9r-descendant. It's really weird. N9t t9 menti9n, he l99ks exactly like me? I mean, kind 9f 96vi9usly? S9 when y9u're hitting 9n him, it's like y9u're hitting 9n me at the exact same time, which like I said. It's weird.
      @kankri_talk:#Trigger-warning#Incest#Anathemas#Viscerality#Vaguely#9ffputting KANKRI: N9t t9 get int9 all this again, 6ut the th9ught 9f dating y9u... it's just a strange and vaguely 9ffputting idea. N9 9ffense. It alm9st makes me understand at a visceral level the 6izarre human anathema 9f incest, which is s9mething I can't really explain. I'm just saying.
      @porrim_annoyed:#Oh-my-Go+d. PORRIM: (Very deep sigh.)
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: I'm S9RRY, 9k? I'm s9rry that I am, perhaps literally, the 9nly 9ne n9t t9 ever fall prey t9 y9ur tireless 9mnidirecti9nal s9licitati9ns, 9r t9 get swept up in 9ne 9f y9ur innumera6le flushed 9r caligin9us flings. I happened t9 always prefer y9u as a friend, and in any case, I always preferred t9 lead a relatively chaste existence, as it keeps me f9cused 9n fighting 9n 6ehalf 9f truly imp9rtant pr96lems. Alth9ugh staying "relatively" chaste t9 y9u I supp9se is n9t saying much.
      @porrim_angry:#Hey. PORRIM: ...
      @kankri_talk4:#TW#Derailment#Train-wrecks#Ch99-ch99-catastr9phes KANKRI: 9nce again, I ap9l9gize. I've 6lundered int9 the pr96lematic territ9ry 9f vacillati9n shaming, thus 9pening the fl99dgates t9 the myriad ways 9ne may 6e disadvantaged up9n 6y its staggering shame radius. I f9rg9t t9 check my piety privilege, and here we are. I was g9ing t9 c9ver this t9pic in a much later chapter 9f my lecture, 6ut we've g9tten 6adly derailed here.
      @kankri_talk2:#Village-tw9-wheel-device KANKRI: Karkat, I'm s9rry f9r this interrupti9n. I pr9mise I'll get 6ack t9 my critical lecture as s99n as this pr9miscu9us 6usy69dy leaves us in peace.
      @karkat_horror KARKAT: 
      @porrim_annoyed PORRIM: Yes, critical lecture. I'm sure.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk:#Yes PORRIM: And am I right in being just as sure yo+u are assiduo+usly deco+nstructing every co+nceivable, hypo+thetical fo+rm o+f injustice no+ matter ho+w o+bscure, except tho+se that I happen to+ think are kind o+f impo+rtant?
      @kankri_talk3:#N9 KANKRI: N9. Just, n9, P9rrim. We're n9t d9ing this.
      @kankri_talk3 KANKRI: I am n9t g9ing t9 p9llute Karkat's utterly imperative crash c9urse, in which he is intr9duced t9 the A6S9LUTE 6ASICS, 6y indulging in y9ur pet issues.
      @porrim_annoyed2:#"HUMAN-SARCASM" PORRIM: Yes, ho+w dreadful it wo+uld be fo+r yo+ur sixty nine millio+n wo+rd essay to+ get bo+gged do+wn by even the faintest reference to+ the ro+les o+f gender in Befo+ran and Alternian civilizatio+n.
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: L99k, it's n9t that I'm insensitive t9 y9ur c9ncerns 9n that t9pic. I'm interested t9 discuss them with y9u 9n an academic, primarily the9retical level.
      @porrim_annoyed2:#... PORRIM: Theo+retical?
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: I just think there is inherent danger in muddying the waters 9f disc9urse 6y intr9ducing s9cial issues which are suspect at 6est, thus c9nsuming crucial res9urces fr9m the limited cache 9f rhet9ric which pr9pels these narratives. And furtherm9re, 9ne c9uld argue it's m9re than a little pr96lematic, 9ffensive even, f9r y9u t9 6e appr9priating the lexic9n 9f sensitivity used t9 advance awareness 9f maj9r issues, thus reducing it t9 the level 6uzzspeak and pseud9science. It makes it m9re difficult f9r th9se 9f us wh9 are genuinely f9cused 9n p9sitive change t9 6e taken seri9usly, that's all.
      @porrim_angry:#That's-no+t#what-that-even#means? PORRIM: Appro+priating??
      @porrim_angry2:#Yo+u-did-no+t-just... PORRIM: PSEUDOSCIENCE???
      @kankri_talk4:#Fr9wned-up9n#Fr9wns-all-ar9und#Welc9me-t9-fr9wn-t9wn KANKRI: I'm s9rry, I just d9n't think there's much there. We aren't like humans, wh9se species 6izarrely en9ugh includes highly specialized r9les f9r 69th sexes in the pr9cess 9f repr9ducti9n, and s9 this naturally had s9cial ramificati9ns f9r the way their civilizati9n ev9lved. 6ut that's n9t h9w it w9rks f9r us, s9 I fail t9 see h9w gender fact9rs int9 the discussi9n in a way that can 6e effectively and rati9nally pr96lematized. Where is the r99m f9r unexamined privilege in the dich9t9my? I d9n't see it. And appr9priating the talking p9ints and awareness-raising tactics f9r du6i9us issues like this is, frankly, fr9wned up9n, t9 put it p9litely. Such appr9priative gestures 9nly serve t9 marginalize and invalidate th9se su6ject t9 seri9us, real life struggles and 9ppressi9n, and I guess I'm a little disapp9inted t9 see y9u 6eing s9 6lithely and inappr9priately appr9priat9ry.
      @porrim_angrytalk:#Trigger-warning:#Abo+ut-to+-kick-yo+ur-tall-pantsed-ass PORRIM: Kanny, I'm starting to+ feel just a little bit triggered by all this "appro+priatio+n" bullshit.
      @kankri_talk:#It's-the-may9r,-right?#G9tta-6e-the-may9r KANKRI: 9h! My sincere ap9l9gies. I sh9uld have d9ne a 6etter j96 tagging my statements, 6ut f9r future reference, it's helpful t9 alert y9ur c9nversati9nal partners t9 y9ur triggers well in advance. Sh9uld I g9 fetch y9ur m9irail t9 help settle y9u d9wn? And if s9, wh9 exactly w9uld 6e filling that quadrant t9day?
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: Alright. Obvio+usly yo+u're in o+ne o+f yo+ur bratty mo+o+ds. I'm go+ne.
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: D9n't 6e like that. Really, we can talk a69ut whatever y9u like later, and I'll 6e really sympathetic, I pr9mise. Just n9t ar9und my pupil while he is still learning. 
      @kankri_talk:#N9w-where-was-I? KANKRI: 9r... my descendant. What did I say? Haha. Karkat, I mean. Anyway, Karkat, again I ap9l9gize f9r that. 
      @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: 
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='kankriTalk4' sprite='porrim' command='talk' name='Be Kankri.'><args>
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: What? Y9u want t9 6e me? What s9rt 9f n9nsense request is that?
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Can't y9u see I'm in the middle 9f a direly imp9rtant w9rd dump? I mean man-t9-man c9nversati9n with Karkat?
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: I might c9nsider it if y9u asked m9re nicely. 9r at the very least, m9re "radically".
      <!--  -->
</args></action>



<action class='latulaTalk5' sprite='kankri' command='talk' name='Talk to Latula.'><args>
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: 9h, hey, Latula. I th9ught I heard y9ur device grinding 9n vari9us surfaces near6y. 
      @kankri_talk:#Did-y9u-hang...#Hang-10?#N9-that-can't-6e-right... KANKRI: H9w are y9ur athletic t9y stunts g9ing? Are y9u getting a l9t 9f... a l9t 9f "air"? Am I saying that right?
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: you knowz 1t bro!!! 
      @latula_stunt LATULA: you c4nt 3v3n TOUCH th1s. 1m 3sc4p1ng to th3 s1d3, from 4bov3, from 3v3ry wh1ch w4y b4s1c4lly!!!!
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: Well, I wasn't g9ing t9 attempt t9 make any s9rt 9f physical c9ntact with y9u, and even if I did, I have n9 d9u6t that y9u w9uld 6e a6le t9 maneuver away fr9m my grasp 9n y9ur speedy little platf9rm. Either way, I'm m9re than c9ntent t9 let y9u escape in any directi9n 9f y9ur ch99sing, if that's y9ur wish.
      @latula_bored LATULA: dud3. just wh3n 1 th1nk youv3 4lr34dy s41d th3 squ4r3st th1ng poss1bl3, you go 4nd s4y som3th1ng l1k3 th4t.
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Haha. I guess. Y9u kn9w, it's really nice we can talk like this.
      @latula_huh:#? LATULA: 1t 1s...
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Yes. I was just thinking lately, a69ut 9ur new p9st-scratch friends. Particularly the y9ung Vantas and Pyr9pe iterati9ns 9n their team, and h9w they're pretty similar t9 us, 6ut als9 really different.
      @latula_happier:#h4v3-u-s33n-h3r-l1l-dr4gon-su1t??-3333!#SO-cut3->8] LATULA: y34h. l1l m3 1s bl1nd! d1d u 3v3n KNOW th4t??
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Yes, 6ut that's n9t really what I'm talking a69ut.
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: She and Karkat have a different relati9nship fr9m the 9ne we have. Theirs is much m9re tur6ulent, which is fueled presuma6ly 6y r9mantic tensi9n. I'm picking up 9n s9me maj9r vascillati9n vi6es fr9m their situati9n. It's kind 9f unf9rtunate, 6ut it makes me grateful that we never g9t t9 that p9int.
      @latula_talk LATULA: h3llz y34h. who n33ds th4t?
      @kankri_talk4:#Seri9usly.#I-mean,-she's-nice,-6ut...#Really? KANKRI: I'm sure it's m9stly due t9 the fact that we've stayed entirely away fr9m the sting6ug's nest 9f r9mantic entanglement. Which 9f c9urse is related t9 my 9ath 9f celi6acy, which as y9u kn9w is just a pers9nal ch9ice, 9ne which f9r s9me reas9n my p9st-scratch adult self eventually strayed fr9m... with... Meulin, 9f all pe9ple? 6ut that's neither here n9r there.
      @latula_laugh:#:3#h3h3h3h LATULA: h4h4h4h4... you 4nd m3uz. st1ll cr4cks m3 up... H4H4H4H4H4H4!!!!
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: Yes. 6ut regardless. What I'm saying is, it's great we stayed away fr9m that. It's helped me appreciate y9u as a friend, and admire all y9ur g99d qualities. Plat9nically, 9f c9urse.
      @latula_happytalk LATULA: your3 r1ght! 1ts b33n pr3tty r4d wh3n you put 1t th4t w4y.
      @kankri_talk3:#Cerulean-savi9rs#Teal-templars#Vi9let-valiants#Purple-paladins KANKRI: Like h9w y9u never 69ught int9 the usual r9les 9f y9ur caste, as an aqua, n9t even the m9re "well intended" s9cial c9nventi9ns 9f y9ur privileged arist9cratic 6l99dline. Y9u never l99ked d9wn 9n any69dy, 9r saw it as y9ur civil duty t9 care f9r 9r "impr9ve" the warmer classes, falling prey t9 unf9rtunate tendencies inv9lving cerulean savi9r c9mplex, 9r the "6lue 6l99d's 6urden" (trigger warning 9n that, 96vi9usly) which sadly 6ecame s9 insepera6le fr9m the fa6ric 9f the spectral 9rder, with each class c9nditi9ned t9 view th9se 6el9w it the same way, the 96stacles t9 raising awareness were alm9st insurm9unta6le. 6ut unlike the c99ler hues 9n 9ur team m9re priviliged than y9u, like y9ur Serkets, y9ur Zahhaks, y9ur Amp9ras... I never g9t the sense that y9u put the slightest 6it 9f st9ck in any 9f that, and I think that's pretty amazing.
      @latula_talk LATULA: uh... y34h! th4t sh1tz 4 dr4g, why would 1 both3r w1th 4ny of th4t? 1 m34n, 1ll h3lp low bloods l34rn stunts 4nd ch34t cod3z 1f th3y w4nt, but th4ts 1t!!!
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: Right. And I'm just saying if my head was ever cl9uded 6y r9mantic feelings f9r y9u, I pr96a6ly w9uldn't 6e a6le t9 appreciate that a69ut y9u.
      @kankri_talk2:#It-rarely-is KANKRI: Just like I w9uldn't 6e a6le t9 appreciate the fairly c99l "zees" y9u put at the end 9f many w9rds, 9r say things l9udly and with enthusiasm, even if it's n9t particularly warranted.
      @latula_happy:#woo! LATULA: h3h3h. y34h!!!!
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: 9r the way y9ur hair fl9ws in the wind when y9u sc99t 9ver s9me s9rt 9f 96stactle 9n y9ur device really fast.
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: 9r the way y9u make this funny little n9ise just as y9u c9nnect with 9ne 9f y9ur c9pi9us high fives, which can 9nly 6e heard 9ver the l9ud slap if y9u listen really cl9sely.
      @latula_idle2 LATULA: um, y34h... 1 not1c3d... som3 stuff l1k3 th4t...
      @latula_happy LATULA: 4bout you too 1 gu3ss?
      @latula_idle:#uh... LATULA: h3h.
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: 9r the way y9u have always sh9wn kindness t9 pe9ple wh9 needed help, with9ut making them feel tragic 9r helpless f9r accepting it.
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: 9r the way y9u still manage t9 l99k stylish even with9ut y9ur c99l shades, 9r s9metimes when they're pr9pped up 9n y9ur head just in fr9nt 9f y9ur h9rns.
      @latula_idle2:#1...#hm LATULA: wh...
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: 9r, I d9n't kn9w if y9u remem6er, that time Meenah 6aked every69dy a cake. It was the first sweep anniversary 9f entering the game, 9ne 9f the rare m9ments 9f s9lidarity and g99d cheer am9ng 9ur entire team at 9nce. Every9ne was raving a69ut h9w g99d the fresh 6aked cake smelled, s9 y9u t99k a 6ig sniff, I guess f9rgetting f9r a m9ment y9u c9uldn't smell. Then y9u quickly caught y9urself, and played it c99l making sure n9 9ne n9ticed, which n9 9ne did. 6ut I n9ticed. And I just th9ught that was kind 9f endearing. 
      @latula_idle3 LATULA: 
      @kankri_talk KANKRI: Anyway, I think all that w9uld have 6een c9mpletely l9st 9n me if we didn't have this str9ng plat9nic 69nd. I just th9ught I'd say that. Guess I'll get g9ing n9w. 
      @kankri_idle KANKRI: See y9u ar9und, Latula.
      @latula_idle3 LATULA: 
      <!--  -->
</args></action>      

<action class='porrimTalk4' sprite='kankri' command='talk' name='Talk to Porrim.'><args>
      @kankri_talk:#Wait,-what-did-I-say?#Definitely-meant-friends KANKRI: In the future, I'll thank y9u n9t t9 em6arrass me in fr9nt 9f my new disciples. Friends. I mean friends.
      @kankri_talk4:#Weird-human-familial-structures KANKRI: I really d9n't need y9u p9licing my awareness-raising rhet9ric. Y9u are n9t my "human m9ther".
      @porrim_surprisetalk PORRIM: What do+es that even mean??
      @kankri_talk3:#I-mean...#en9rm9us-in-pr9gressive-virtue KANKRI: Y9u w9uld understand if y9u spent time actually researching 9ther cultures t9 gain a m9re c9mprehensive f9undati9nal perspective 9n 9ur systemic pr96lems instead 9f meddling in 9ther pe9ple's enlightening and en9rm9us c9nversati9ns.
      @porrim_talk PORRIM: All these sweeps and yo+u still act like such a wiggler so+metimes. Hey... is that...
      @porrim_annoyed PORRIM: Is that grub sauce o+n yo+ur face?
      @kankri_idle KANKRI: What? N9.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Yes it is. Yo+u have a big smudge o+f sauce, right there. Yo+u're a mess, Kanny. Co+me here.
      @kankri_rage:#SEE???#It's-fine KANKRI: N9! N9, st9p. D9n't t9uch me, I g9t it!
      @porrim_angry2:#Gho+st-laundry PORRIM: Do+n't wipe it o+ff with yo+ur sleeve! Oh my Go+d. I JUST washed that fo+r yo+u.
      @kankri_talk4:#9r-Alternian#9r-Earthly KANKRI: I d9n't care. I didn't ask y9u t9 wash my sweater. I keep telling y9u, I have n9 interest in 6ef9ran p9ssessi9ns.
      @porrim_angry2 PORRIM: We aren't o+n Befo+rus anymo+re. I wo+rked hard o+n that sweater, and I'm no+t go+ing to+ stand by while yo+u encrust it in grub sauce.
      @kankri_talk3:#Y9u-can't-even-see-my-nice-6elt KANKRI: I was perfectly happy with9ut the sweater! T9 6e h9nest, I'm less than thrilled with h9w it 96scures my pant line.
      @porrim_angry:#Yo+u-make-me-sigh-so+-much#I'm-almo+st-left-sighless PORRIM: Sigh...
      @porrim_annoyed2 PORRIM: Why are yo+u always so+ co+ntrary with me? To+ be ho+nest, I think yo+ur need to+ "rebel" against whatever I suggest is what drives yo+ur dismissal o+f my views mo+re than anything abo+ut the views themselves.
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: I d9n't dismiss y9ur views. I respect them. I have T9LD y9u this. 
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: I think the r9le 9f gender in 6ef9ran s9ciety is pr96a6ly a really fascinating and advanced su6ject t9 expl9re. See, y9u and I can appreciate the su6ject, 9f c9urse. I just d9n't think any9ne is ready f9r that yet. There are s9 many 9ther hurdles t9 9verc9me first.
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Hurdles? Kanny, yo+u sho+uld serio+usly sto+p o+verthinking this stuff. Even I do+n't kno+w what yo+u're talking abo+ut mo+st o+f the time.
      @kankri_talk2 KANKRI: L99k, I'm just saying, it's a huge risk 9pening that can 9f dirt n99dles, trying t9 educate pe9ple 9n that su6ject 9n t9p 9f everything else. I just d9n't want t9 distract fr9m all the m9re glaring issues that desperately need the full attenti9n 9f 9ur pe9ple if we are g9ing t9 make any pr9gress as a civilizati9n.
      @porrim_surprise PORRIM: Pro+gress as a civilizatio+n?
      @porrim_annoyedtalk PORRIM: Kankri. Our peo+ple are extinct, and yo+u're wo+rried abo+ut "distracting fro+m the mo+re glaring issues"??
      @porrim_angrytalk PORRIM: EVERYONE IS DEAD!!!
      @kankri_talk4 KANKRI: P9rrim, I'm very disapp9inted t9 hear y9u say that.
      @kankri_talk4:#C9rp9realn9rmativity#M9rtality-privilege#S9ul-shaming KANKRI: That was an extremely c9rp9realn9rmative remark.
      @porrim_angry PORRIM: ...
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

<action class='grindTalk'><args>
@latula_idle LATULA: th4t w4s...
@latula_idle2 LATULA: so...
@latula_idle3 LATULA: fr3ak1ng...
@latula_happier:#>8O!!!! LATULA: R44444444444444D1C4L!!!
@latula_shades2 LATULA: holy smok3z grl, 1 d1dnt th1nk you 3v3n h4d gr1ndz l1k3 th4t.
@latula_shine LATULA: so you s4y you w4nn4 b3 m3 huh? w3ll, you got 1t! h3llz grl, 1m not sur3 1f 1 shouldnt b3 th3 on3 4sk1ng to b3 YOU!!!
</args></action>

    <!-- if you examine locked door while karkat is following -->



  <!-- if kankri talks to karkat -->
<action class='karkatTalk1' sprite='kankri' command='talk' name='Talk to Karkat.'><args>
      @kankri_talk:#"6r6" KANKRI: 9ne m9ment please, Karkat. I'm g9ing t9 wander ar9und 6riefly, in an aut9n9m9us fashi9n. I kn9w y9u're very excited t9 c9ntinue 9ur discussi9n, and I pr9mise I'll return very sh9rtly s9 that we may resume. Just remain standing here in this exact sp9t, while y9u take time t9 let the wisd9m 9f my w9rds take r99t in y9ur heart, and try n9t t9 wander 9ff with any69dy, 9k? 6e right 6ack.

      @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: 
      <!--  -->
</args></action>

   

  
<!-- if you try to leave the room as a non-meenah character -->
<action class='exitAlert' command='talk'><args>
      @!:#nice-try Where do you think YOU'RE going! This is Meenah's interactive quest through the afterlife. You can only leave this area if you're being her!
</args></action>

      <!-- if you examine locked door -->
<action class='doorTalk1' command='talk' name='Open door.'><args>
      @!:#mysterious-symbol#a-clue#bonus-hint:#it's-karkat The door is locked. It appears to be guarding someone's private memories. Looks like it needs a password. You wonder who locked it?
      <!--  -->
</args></action>
      
	</classes>
</sburb>
